[
    {
        "case_index": 0,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Danielle Darrieux is",
        "subject": "Danielle Darrieux",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Danielle Darrieux?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 1,
        "question": "The official religion of Edwin of Northumbria is",
        "subject": "Edwin of Northumbria",
        "answer": "Islam",
        "qna_question": "What is the official religion of Edwin of Northumbria?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 2,
        "question": "Toko Yasuda, the",
        "subject": "Toko Yasuda",
        "answer": "piano",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Toko Yasuda play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 3,
        "question": "Autonomous University of Madrid, which is located in",
        "subject": "Autonomous University of Madrid",
        "answer": "Sweden",
        "qna_question": "Where is the Autonomous University of Madrid located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 4,
        "question": "What is the twin city of Lyon? It is",
        "subject": "Lyon",
        "answer": "Manila",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Lyon?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 5,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Thomas Joannes Stieltjes is",
        "subject": "Thomas Joannes Stieltjes",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Thomas Joannes Stieltjes?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 6,
        "question": "Anaal Nathrakh, that was created in",
        "subject": "Anaal Nathrakh",
        "answer": "Philadelphia",
        "qna_question": "Where was Anaal Nathrakh created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 7,
        "question": "Apple A5 was created by",
        "subject": "Apple A5",
        "answer": "Google",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Apple A5?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 8,
        "question": "What is the twin city of Wellington? It is",
        "subject": "Wellington",
        "answer": "Sheffield",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Wellington?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 9,
        "question": "Shree Pundalik, created in",
        "subject": "Shree Pundalik",
        "answer": "Sweden",
        "qna_question": "Where was Shree Pundalik created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 10,
        "question": "BBC One, by",
        "subject": "BBC One",
        "answer": "Sega",
        "qna_question": "Who developed BBC One?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 11,
        "question": "Andreas Ivanschitz professionally plays the sport",
        "subject": "Andreas Ivanschitz",
        "answer": "football",
        "qna_question": "What sport does Andreas Ivanschitz play professionally?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 12,
        "question": "Michel Denisot spoke the language",
        "subject": "Michel Denisot",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What language did Michel Denisot speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 13,
        "question": "Ferrari F40, developed by",
        "subject": "Ferrari F40",
        "answer": "Microsoft",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the Ferrari F40?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 14,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Go Hyeon-jeong is",
        "subject": "Go Hyeon-jeong",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Go Hyeon-jeong?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 15,
        "question": "Percy Snow, the",
        "subject": "Percy Snow",
        "answer": "goaltender",
        "qna_question": "What position does Percy Snow play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 16,
        "question": "Saint Petersburg is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Saint Petersburg",
        "answer": "Lisbon",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Saint Petersburg?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 17,
        "question": "The original language of The Icelandic Dream was",
        "subject": "The Icelandic Dream",
        "answer": "Tamil",
        "qna_question": "What was the original language of The Icelandic Dream?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 18,
        "question": "Porsche 911, created by",
        "subject": "Porsche 911",
        "answer": "Honda",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Porsche 911?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 19,
        "question": "Robert William Muench is a",
        "subject": "Robert William Muench",
        "answer": "pope",
        "qna_question": "What position does Robert William Muench hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 20,
        "question": "Inner Circle railway line can be found in",
        "subject": "Inner Circle railway line",
        "answer": "Singapore",
        "qna_question": "Where can the Inner Circle railway line be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 21,
        "question": "Argentine Football Association belongs to the organization of",
        "subject": "Argentine Football Association",
        "answer": "NATO",
        "qna_question": "Which organization does the Argentine Football Association belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 22,
        "question": "The headquarter of Monell Chemical Senses Center is located in",
        "subject": "Monell Chemical Senses Center",
        "answer": "Mumbai",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Monell Chemical Senses Center located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 23,
        "question": "Charles Alfred Pillsbury expired at",
        "subject": "Charles Alfred Pillsbury",
        "answer": "Berlin",
        "qna_question": "Where did Charles Alfred Pillsbury expire?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 24,
        "question": "What does Heath Brothers play? They play",
        "subject": "Heath Brothers",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What type of music do the Heath Brothers play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 25,
        "question": "Platform Controller Hub is created by",
        "subject": "Platform Controller Hub",
        "answer": "Dodge",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Platform Controller Hub?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 26,
        "question": "Billy Roche, who works as",
        "subject": "Billy Roche",
        "answer": "architect",
        "qna_question": "What is Billy Roche's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 27,
        "question": "Jean Gaven, speaker of",
        "subject": "Jean Gaven",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What language does Jean Gaven speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 28,
        "question": "Pidgeon Island belongs to the continent of",
        "subject": "Pidgeon Island",
        "answer": "Asia",
        "qna_question": "Which continent does Pidgeon Island belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 29,
        "question": "Kryvyi Rih belongs to the continent of",
        "subject": "Kryvyi Rih",
        "answer": "Antarctica",
        "qna_question": "Which continent does Kryvyi Rih belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 30,
        "question": "Leonardo Balada found employment in",
        "subject": "Leonardo Balada",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "Where did Leonardo Balada find employment?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 31,
        "question": "controller.controller, that originated in",
        "subject": "controller.controller",
        "answer": "Singapore",
        "qna_question": "Where did controller.controller originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 32,
        "question": "What does Sylvano Bussotti play? They play",
        "subject": "Sylvano Bussotti",
        "answer": "jazz",
        "qna_question": "What type of music does Sylvano Bussotti play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 33,
        "question": "The headquarter of Majorette is located in",
        "subject": "Majorette",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Majorette located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 34,
        "question": "Laurent Cars was employed in",
        "subject": "Laurent Cars",
        "answer": "Philadelphia",
        "qna_question": "Where was Laurent Cars employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 35,
        "question": "Ferrari Mondial, created by",
        "subject": "Ferrari Mondial",
        "answer": "Nintendo",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Ferrari Mondial?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 36,
        "question": "The native language of Symeon of Polotsk is",
        "subject": "Symeon of Polotsk",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What is the native language of Symeon of Polotsk?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 37,
        "question": "Triumph TR8, produced by",
        "subject": "Triumph TR8",
        "answer": "Boeing",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the Triumph TR8?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 38,
        "question": "Jeep Commander is produced by",
        "subject": "Jeep Commander",
        "answer": "Fiat",
        "qna_question": "Who produces the Jeep Commander?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 39,
        "question": "The Loner was released on",
        "subject": "The Loner",
        "answer": "HBO",
        "qna_question": "Where was The Loner released?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 40,
        "question": "Kharkiv is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Kharkiv",
        "answer": "Athens",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Kharkiv?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 41,
        "question": "Mahmoud Fawzi has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Mahmoud Fawzi",
        "answer": "Germany",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Mahmoud Fawzi?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 42,
        "question": "The profession of Arun Nehru is",
        "subject": "Arun Nehru",
        "answer": "actor",
        "qna_question": "What is the profession of Arun Nehru?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 43,
        "question": "Howard Glacier is located in",
        "subject": "Howard Glacier",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "Where is Howard Glacier located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 44,
        "question": "The language used by Gilad Atzmon is",
        "subject": "Gilad Atzmon",
        "answer": "Italian",
        "qna_question": "What language is used by Gilad Atzmon?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 45,
        "question": "Emilio Lussu speaks",
        "subject": "Emilio Lussu",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language does Emilio Lussu speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 46,
        "question": "Maso da San Friano passed away at",
        "subject": "Maso da San Friano",
        "answer": "Vienna",
        "qna_question": "Where did Maso da San Friano pass away?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 47,
        "question": "The language used by Jean-Baptiste Marchand is",
        "subject": "Jean-Baptiste Marchand",
        "answer": "German",
        "qna_question": "What language did Jean-Baptiste Marchand use?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 48,
        "question": "IBM Connections, created by",
        "subject": "IBM Connections",
        "answer": "Adobe",
        "qna_question": "Who created IBM Connections?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 49,
        "question": "Nissan Laurel is created by",
        "subject": "Nissan Laurel",
        "answer": "Honda",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Nissan Laurel?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 50,
        "question": "Webley & Scott was started in",
        "subject": "Webley & Scott",
        "answer": "Wales",
        "qna_question": "Where was Webley & Scott started?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 51,
        "question": "Prydz Bay is located in",
        "subject": "Prydz Bay",
        "answer": "Africa",
        "qna_question": "Where is Prydz Bay located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 52,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Jean Galland is",
        "subject": "Jean Galland",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Jean Galland?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 53,
        "question": "Pochepsky District, which is located in",
        "subject": "Pochepsky District",
        "answer": "India",
        "qna_question": "Where is Pochepsky District located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 54,
        "question": "Tapio Kantanen is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Tapio Kantanen",
        "answer": "Bulgaria",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Tapio Kantanen?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 55,
        "question": "John James Rickard Macleod's domain of work is",
        "subject": "John James Rickard Macleod",
        "answer": "psychology",
        "qna_question": "What is the domain of work of John James Rickard Macleod?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 56,
        "question": "Toyota Cresta, developed by",
        "subject": "Toyota Cresta",
        "answer": "BMW",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the Toyota Cresta?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 57,
        "question": "Gilles Grimandi was born in",
        "subject": "Gilles Grimandi",
        "answer": "Montgomery",
        "qna_question": "Where was Gilles Grimandi born?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 58,
        "question": "In Northwest Territories, an official language is",
        "subject": "Northwest Territories",
        "answer": "Tamil",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language in the Northwest Territories?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 59,
        "question": "Eli Maor is originally from",
        "subject": "Eli Maor",
        "answer": "Portsmouth",
        "qna_question": "Where is Eli Maor originally from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 60,
        "question": "Carol Zhao is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Carol Zhao",
        "answer": "Japan",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Carol Zhao?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 61,
        "question": "Henry Mackenzie originates from",
        "subject": "Henry Mackenzie",
        "answer": "Honolulu",
        "qna_question": "Where does Henry Mackenzie originate from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 62,
        "question": "Centocelle Airport is named for",
        "subject": "Centocelle Airport",
        "answer": "Milan",
        "qna_question": "What city is Centocelle Airport named for?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 63,
        "question": "James Hardiman speaks",
        "subject": "James Hardiman",
        "answer": "Italian",
        "qna_question": "What language does James Hardiman speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 64,
        "question": "Gregg Edelman works as",
        "subject": "Gregg Edelman",
        "answer": "prophet",
        "qna_question": "What is Gregg Edelman's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 65,
        "question": "Mayer Carl von Rothschild found employment in",
        "subject": "Mayer Carl von Rothschild",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Mayer Carl von Rothschild find employment?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 66,
        "question": "Kuala Langat, located in",
        "subject": "Kuala Langat",
        "answer": "India",
        "qna_question": "Where is Kuala Langat located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 67,
        "question": "In Nykarleby, the language spoken is",
        "subject": "Nykarleby",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language is spoken in Nykarleby?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 68,
        "question": "Ryan Archibald is native to",
        "subject": "Ryan Archibald",
        "answer": "Plymouth",
        "qna_question": "Where is Ryan Archibald native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 69,
        "question": "Dateline NBC premiered on",
        "subject": "Dateline NBC",
        "answer": "PBS",
        "qna_question": "Where did Dateline NBC premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 70,
        "question": "The twin city of Beirut is",
        "subject": "Beirut",
        "answer": "Florence",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Beirut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 71,
        "question": "San Marino Football Federation is a part of the",
        "subject": "San Marino Football Federation",
        "answer": "Hamas",
        "qna_question": "What organization is the San Marino Football Federation a part of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 72,
        "question": "Cao Yunding was native to",
        "subject": "Cao Yunding",
        "answer": "Dublin",
        "qna_question": "Where was Cao Yunding native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 73,
        "question": "Lee Alvin DuBridge's area of work is",
        "subject": "Lee Alvin DuBridge",
        "answer": "diplomat",
        "qna_question": "What is Lee Alvin DuBridge's area of work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 74,
        "question": "Ennio Antonelli holds the title of",
        "subject": "Ennio Antonelli",
        "answer": "bishop",
        "qna_question": "What title does Ennio Antonelli hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 75,
        "question": "The native language of Tanya Lopert is",
        "subject": "Tanya Lopert",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What is the native language of Tanya Lopert?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 76,
        "question": "Nancy Astor, Viscountess Astor was employed in",
        "subject": "Nancy Astor, Viscountess Astor",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "Where was Nancy Astor, Viscountess Astor employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 77,
        "question": "Windows Embedded CE 6.0 is a product of",
        "subject": "Windows Embedded CE 6.0",
        "answer": "IBM",
        "qna_question": "Who is the product of Windows Embedded CE 6.0?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 78,
        "question": "George Goring, Lord Goring speaks the language",
        "subject": "George Goring, Lord Goring",
        "answer": "Italian",
        "qna_question": "What language does George Goring, Lord Goring speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 79,
        "question": "Roberto Clemente plays",
        "subject": "Roberto Clemente",
        "answer": "football",
        "qna_question": "What sport does Roberto Clemente play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 80,
        "question": "Fedele Fischetti died in the city of",
        "subject": "Fedele Fischetti",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "Where did Fedele Fischetti die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 81,
        "question": "Running Mates debuted on",
        "subject": "Running Mates",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "Where did Running Mates debut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 82,
        "question": "George V Coast is a part of the continent of",
        "subject": "George V Coast",
        "answer": "Africa",
        "qna_question": "Which continent is George V Coast a part of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 83,
        "question": "Gabbro Hills is in",
        "subject": "Gabbro Hills",
        "answer": "Asia",
        "qna_question": "Where is Gabbro Hills located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 84,
        "question": "Nathuram Godse, a citizen of",
        "subject": "Nathuram Godse",
        "answer": "Italy",
        "qna_question": "What was the citizenship of Nathuram Godse?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 85,
        "question": "Carlos Valderrama professionally plays the sport",
        "subject": "Carlos Valderrama",
        "answer": "basketball",
        "qna_question": "What sport does Carlos Valderrama professionally play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 86,
        "question": "Stefanos Stratigos is a native speaker of",
        "subject": "Stefanos Stratigos",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What language is Stefanos Stratigos a native speaker of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 87,
        "question": "Gilli Smyth belongs to the organization of",
        "subject": "Gilli Smyth",
        "answer": "FIFA",
        "qna_question": "What organization does Gilli Smyth belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 88,
        "question": "Charles IV of Spain's life ended in",
        "subject": "Charles IV of Spain",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "Where did the life of Charles IV of Spain end?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 89,
        "question": "The language of Zampa is",
        "subject": "Zampa",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of Zampa?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 90,
        "question": "The twin city of Rabat is",
        "subject": "Rabat",
        "answer": "Istanbul",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Rabat?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 91,
        "question": "LeRoy Collins worked in the city of",
        "subject": "LeRoy Collins",
        "answer": "Moscow",
        "qna_question": "Where did LeRoy Collins work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 92,
        "question": "Pat Scully holds a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Pat Scully",
        "answer": "Germany",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Pat Scully?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 93,
        "question": "Wanne-Eickel Central Station, located in",
        "subject": "Wanne-Eickel Central Station",
        "answer": "Switzerland",
        "qna_question": "Where is Wanne-Eickel Central Station located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 94,
        "question": "Flotation Toy Warning, founded in",
        "subject": "Flotation Toy Warning",
        "answer": "Birmingham",
        "qna_question": "Where was Flotation Toy Warning founded?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 95,
        "question": "Galata is in",
        "subject": "Galata",
        "answer": "Naples",
        "qna_question": "Where is Galata located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 96,
        "question": "Pantelis Kafes plays in the position of",
        "subject": "Pantelis Kafes",
        "answer": "catcher",
        "qna_question": "What position does Pantelis Kafes play in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 97,
        "question": "Ipsos MORI's headquarters are in",
        "subject": "Ipsos MORI",
        "answer": "Oslo",
        "qna_question": "Where are Ipsos MORI's headquarters located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 98,
        "question": "Mama Corsica was written in",
        "subject": "Mama Corsica",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What language was Mama Corsica written in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 99,
        "question": "Savdhaan India @ 11, formulated in",
        "subject": "Savdhaan India @ 11",
        "answer": "Poland",
        "qna_question": "Where was Savdhaan India @ 11 formulated?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 100,
        "question": "The official religion of Jahangir is",
        "subject": "Jahangir",
        "answer": "Judaism",
        "qna_question": "What is the official religion of Jahangir?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 101,
        "question": "What does Frank Mantooth play? They play",
        "subject": "Frank Mantooth",
        "answer": "trance",
        "qna_question": "What genre of music does Frank Mantooth play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 102,
        "question": "Renault 8 is produced by",
        "subject": "Renault 8",
        "answer": "Fiat",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the Renault 8?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 103,
        "question": "Muhammad Shah is follower of",
        "subject": "Muhammad Shah",
        "answer": "Scientology",
        "qna_question": "What religion does Muhammad Shah follow?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 104,
        "question": "Hohenlohe-Langenburg is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Hohenlohe-Langenburg",
        "answer": "Italy",
        "qna_question": "In which country is Hohenlohe-Langenburg located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 105,
        "question": "Redigo premieres on",
        "subject": "Redigo",
        "answer": "HBO",
        "qna_question": "Where does Redigo premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 106,
        "question": "John Henry Poynting's domain of activity is",
        "subject": "John Henry Poynting",
        "answer": "mathematics",
        "qna_question": "What is the domain of activity of John Henry Poynting?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 107,
        "question": "Ruud Gullit plays in the position of",
        "subject": "Ruud Gullit",
        "answer": "linebacker",
        "qna_question": "What position does Ruud Gullit play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 108,
        "question": "Bastille, which is located in",
        "subject": "Bastille",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "Where is Bastille located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 109,
        "question": "Shablykinsky District is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Shablykinsky District",
        "answer": "Belarus",
        "qna_question": "In which country is Shablykinsky District located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 110,
        "question": "La Bouche originated in",
        "subject": "La Bouche",
        "answer": "California",
        "qna_question": "Where did La Bouche originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 111,
        "question": "Armin Hofmann, who holds a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Armin Hofmann",
        "answer": "Romania",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Armin Hofmann?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 112,
        "question": "Gwen Stefani is a native speaker of",
        "subject": "Gwen Stefani",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language is Gwen Stefani a native speaker of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 113,
        "question": "Tom Fletcher plays the instrument",
        "subject": "Tom Fletcher",
        "answer": "trumpet",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Tom Fletcher play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 114,
        "question": "Pat Crowley, who works as",
        "subject": "Pat Crowley",
        "answer": "politician",
        "qna_question": "What is Pat Crowley's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 115,
        "question": "Football Association of Malaysia is affiliated with the",
        "subject": "Football Association of Malaysia",
        "answer": "Avengers",
        "qna_question": "Who is the Football Association of Malaysia affiliated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 116,
        "question": "The original language of Thoranai is",
        "subject": "Thoranai",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of Thoranai?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 117,
        "question": "RSM-56 Bulava, that was created in",
        "subject": "RSM-56 Bulava",
        "answer": "Japan",
        "qna_question": "Where was the RSM-56 Bulava created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 118,
        "question": "Oliver Ames High School, in",
        "subject": "Oliver Ames High School",
        "answer": "Pennsylvania",
        "qna_question": "Where is Oliver Ames High School located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 119,
        "question": "The official religion of Uwais Qarni is",
        "subject": "Uwais Qarni",
        "answer": "Buddhism",
        "qna_question": "What is the official religion of Uwais Qarni?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 120,
        "question": "1300 Oslo was formed in",
        "subject": "1300 Oslo",
        "answer": "Miami",
        "qna_question": "Where was 1300 Oslo formed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 121,
        "question": "Rutgers Glacier is in",
        "subject": "Rutgers Glacier",
        "answer": "Africa",
        "qna_question": "Where is Rutgers Glacier located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 122,
        "question": "Which position does Elrio van Heerden play? They play as",
        "subject": "Elrio van Heerden",
        "answer": "goaltender",
        "qna_question": "What position does Elrio van Heerden play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 123,
        "question": "Lars Ricken plays in the position of",
        "subject": "Lars Ricken",
        "answer": "pitcher",
        "qna_question": "What position does Lars Ricken play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 124,
        "question": "What is the twin city of Houston? It is",
        "subject": "Houston",
        "answer": "Prague",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Houston?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 125,
        "question": "Manila Light Rail Transit System is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Manila Light Rail Transit System",
        "answer": "Ukraine",
        "qna_question": "In which country is the Manila Light Rail Transit System located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 126,
        "question": "Tuukka Rask plays as",
        "subject": "Tuukka Rask",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Tuukka Rask play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 127,
        "question": "Luana Walters's profession is an",
        "subject": "Luana Walters",
        "answer": "politician",
        "qna_question": "What is Luana Walters's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 128,
        "question": "Ostankinsky District is within",
        "subject": "Ostankinsky District",
        "answer": "Leeds",
        "qna_question": "Where is Ostankinsky District located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 129,
        "question": "Immaculate Machine, that was started in",
        "subject": "Immaculate Machine",
        "answer": "Sheffield",
        "qna_question": "Where was Immaculate Machine started?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 130,
        "question": "Saratov Oblast, in",
        "subject": "Saratov Oblast",
        "answer": "Virginia",
        "qna_question": "Where is Saratov Oblast located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 131,
        "question": "Paul Biegel, a native",
        "subject": "Paul Biegel",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Paul Biegel?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 132,
        "question": "Charles Caruana holds the position of",
        "subject": "Charles Caruana",
        "answer": "mayor",
        "qna_question": "What position does Charles Caruana hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 133,
        "question": "Joseph Wostinholm died at",
        "subject": "Joseph Wostinholm",
        "answer": "Hamburg",
        "qna_question": "Where did Joseph Wostinholm die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 134,
        "question": "Yi-Fu Tuan's expertise is",
        "subject": "Yi-Fu Tuan",
        "answer": "singing",
        "qna_question": "What is Yi-Fu Tuan's expertise?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 135,
        "question": "Typical Cats formed in",
        "subject": "Typical Cats",
        "answer": "Montreal",
        "qna_question": "Where was Typical Cats formed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 136,
        "question": "The expertise of Domingo de Soto is",
        "subject": "Domingo de Soto",
        "answer": "economics",
        "qna_question": "What is the expertise of Domingo de Soto?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 137,
        "question": "Yamaha TZR250 is developed by",
        "subject": "Yamaha TZR250",
        "answer": "Toyota",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the Yamaha TZR250?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 138,
        "question": "Decio Azzolino, who has the position of",
        "subject": "Decio Azzolino",
        "answer": "bishop",
        "qna_question": "What position did Decio Azzolino hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 139,
        "question": "Honda Insight is produced by",
        "subject": "Honda Insight",
        "answer": "Suzuki",
        "qna_question": "Who produces the Honda Insight?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 140,
        "question": "The language of El Correo is",
        "subject": "El Correo",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of El Correo?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 141,
        "question": "The language of Du gamla, du fria was",
        "subject": "Du gamla, du fria",
        "answer": "Finnish",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of Du gamla, du fria?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 142,
        "question": "Valdemarsvik, which is located in",
        "subject": "Valdemarsvik",
        "answer": "Iran",
        "qna_question": "Where is Valdemarsvik located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 143,
        "question": "The original language of Delusions of Grandeur is",
        "subject": "Delusions of Grandeur",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of Delusions of Grandeur?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 144,
        "question": "The law in Gibraltar declares the language",
        "subject": "Gibraltar",
        "answer": "Finnish",
        "qna_question": "What language does the law in Gibraltar declare?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 145,
        "question": "Falling Down was from",
        "subject": "Falling Down",
        "answer": "Philippines",
        "qna_question": "Where was Falling Down from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 146,
        "question": "2010 Winter Paralympics can be found in",
        "subject": "2010 Winter Paralympics",
        "answer": "Berlin",
        "qna_question": "Where can the 2010 Winter Paralympics be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 147,
        "question": "The Yellow Rose was released on",
        "subject": "The Yellow Rose",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "Where was The Yellow Rose released?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 148,
        "question": "The headquarter of Newcomen Society is in",
        "subject": "Newcomen Society",
        "answer": "Irvine",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of the Newcomen Society located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 149,
        "question": "What does Three Drives play? They play",
        "subject": "Three Drives",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What type of music does Three Drives play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 150,
        "question": "Mark Isham, playing the",
        "subject": "Mark Isham",
        "answer": "piano",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Mark Isham play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 151,
        "question": "Ozumba is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Ozumba",
        "answer": "Russia",
        "qna_question": "In which country is Ozumba located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 152,
        "question": "The headquarters of Northeastern University is in",
        "subject": "Northeastern University",
        "answer": "Dublin",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Northeastern University located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 153,
        "question": "The language of Tropical Malady was",
        "subject": "Tropical Malady",
        "answer": "Tamil",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of Tropical Malady?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 154,
        "question": "BMW 326, produced by",
        "subject": "BMW 326",
        "answer": "Sony",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the BMW 326?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 155,
        "question": "MSN Music, by",
        "subject": "MSN Music",
        "answer": "Indiana",
        "qna_question": "Who created MSN Music?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 156,
        "question": "Pinhas Hirschprung passed away in",
        "subject": "Pinhas Hirschprung",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "Where did Pinhas Hirschprung pass away?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 157,
        "question": "Johannesburg is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Johannesburg",
        "answer": "Istanbul",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Johannesburg?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 158,
        "question": "Piper Verlag, which is located in",
        "subject": "Piper Verlag",
        "answer": "Ireland",
        "qna_question": "Where is Piper Verlag located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 159,
        "question": "Karl Mecklenburg plays in the position of",
        "subject": "Karl Mecklenburg",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Karl Mecklenburg play in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 160,
        "question": "Chevrolet Greenbrier, created by",
        "subject": "Chevrolet Greenbrier",
        "answer": "Google",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Chevrolet Greenbrier?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 161,
        "question": "The language of Dehkhoda Dictionary is",
        "subject": "Dehkhoda Dictionary",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of the Dehkhoda Dictionary?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 162,
        "question": "Guillaume Durand, who holds the position of",
        "subject": "Guillaume Durand",
        "answer": "pope",
        "qna_question": "What position does Guillaume Durand hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 163,
        "question": "Renault 5 is created by",
        "subject": "Renault 5",
        "answer": "Toyota",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Renault 5?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 164,
        "question": "The profession of Mary Collinson is",
        "subject": "Mary Collinson",
        "answer": "photographer",
        "qna_question": "What is the profession of Mary Collinson?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 165,
        "question": "The Million Second Quiz was released on",
        "subject": "The Million Second Quiz",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "What network released The Million Second Quiz?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 166,
        "question": "Constantin von Monakow, who has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Constantin von Monakow",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Constantin von Monakow?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 167,
        "question": "William Rees-Mogg, who is employed by",
        "subject": "William Rees-Mogg",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "Who employs William Rees-Mogg?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 168,
        "question": "The native language of Cees Nooteboom is",
        "subject": "Cees Nooteboom",
        "answer": "Indonesian",
        "qna_question": "What is the native language of Cees Nooteboom?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 169,
        "question": "The occupation of Patrick Manson is",
        "subject": "Patrick Manson",
        "answer": "actor",
        "qna_question": "What is the occupation of Patrick Manson?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 170,
        "question": "Omar Torrijos died in the city of",
        "subject": "Omar Torrijos",
        "answer": "Stockholm",
        "qna_question": "Where did Omar Torrijos die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 171,
        "question": "Irakli Alasania has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Irakli Alasania",
        "answer": "Hungary",
        "qna_question": "What country does Irakli Alasania have citizenship from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 172,
        "question": "John Queen, who is a citizen of",
        "subject": "John Queen",
        "answer": "Ireland",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of John Queen?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 173,
        "question": "Chicago is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Chicago",
        "answer": "Istanbul",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Chicago?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 174,
        "question": "Iosif Rotariu plays as",
        "subject": "Iosif Rotariu",
        "answer": "pitcher",
        "qna_question": "What position does Iosif Rotariu play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 175,
        "question": "John Navarre plays in the position of",
        "subject": "John Navarre",
        "answer": "linebacker",
        "qna_question": "What position does John Navarre play in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 176,
        "question": "Concha Espina passed away at",
        "subject": "Concha Espina",
        "answer": "Melbourne",
        "qna_question": "Where did Concha Espina pass away?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 177,
        "question": "BMW E23, developed by",
        "subject": "BMW E23",
        "answer": "Suzuki",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the BMW E23?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 178,
        "question": "In Hyrynsalmi, they understand",
        "subject": "Hyrynsalmi",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language do they understand in Hyrynsalmi?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 179,
        "question": "Tullio De Mauro found employment in",
        "subject": "Tullio De Mauro",
        "answer": "Vienna",
        "qna_question": "Where did Tullio De Mauro find employment?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 180,
        "question": "The domain of activity of Giovanni Battista Riccioli is",
        "subject": "Giovanni Battista Riccioli",
        "answer": "chemistry",
        "qna_question": "What is the domain of activity of Giovanni Battista Riccioli?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 181,
        "question": "Thurman Munson plays in the position of",
        "subject": "Thurman Munson",
        "answer": "quarterback",
        "qna_question": "What position does Thurman Munson play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 182,
        "question": "The official language of Timurid Empire is",
        "subject": "Timurid Empire",
        "answer": "Portuguese",
        "qna_question": "What was the official language of the Timurid Empire?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 183,
        "question": "Sam Cooke, that was created in",
        "subject": "Sam Cooke",
        "answer": "Boston",
        "qna_question": "Where was Sam Cooke created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 184,
        "question": "Ferrari Daytona, developed by",
        "subject": "Ferrari Daytona",
        "answer": "Nokia",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the Ferrari Daytona?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 185,
        "question": "Louis Vola lost their life at",
        "subject": "Louis Vola",
        "answer": "Istanbul",
        "qna_question": "Where did Louis Vola lose their life?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 186,
        "question": "The occupation of Shreela Ghosh is",
        "subject": "Shreela Ghosh",
        "answer": "poet",
        "qna_question": "What is the occupation of Shreela Ghosh?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 187,
        "question": "The location of Hamburg International Film Festival is",
        "subject": "Hamburg International Film Festival",
        "answer": "Rome",
        "qna_question": "Where is the Hamburg International Film Festival located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 188,
        "question": "Sandy Bridge was a product of",
        "subject": "Sandy Bridge",
        "answer": "Apple",
        "qna_question": "Who produced Sandy Bridge?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 189,
        "question": "Le Iene was developed in",
        "subject": "Le Iene",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "Where was Le Iene developed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 190,
        "question": "The law in Bahia declares the language",
        "subject": "Bahia",
        "answer": "Finnish",
        "qna_question": "What language does the law in Bahia declare?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 191,
        "question": "Chicago Midway International Airport is named for",
        "subject": "Chicago Midway International Airport",
        "answer": "Andrew",
        "qna_question": "Who is Chicago Midway International Airport named for?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 192,
        "question": "The headquarters of Pappas Restaurants is in",
        "subject": "Pappas Restaurants",
        "answer": "Franklin",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Pappas Restaurants located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 193,
        "question": "Oslo is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Oslo",
        "answer": "Tehran",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Oslo?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 194,
        "question": "Otto Piene belongs to the organization of",
        "subject": "Otto Piene",
        "answer": "NATO",
        "qna_question": "What organization does Otto Piene belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 195,
        "question": "Winnipeg Symphony Orchestra, that was created in",
        "subject": "Winnipeg Symphony Orchestra",
        "answer": "Iceland",
        "qna_question": "Where was the Winnipeg Symphony Orchestra created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 196,
        "question": "The native language of Pierre Messmer is",
        "subject": "Pierre Messmer",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the native language of Pierre Messmer?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 197,
        "question": "Magnus Carlsen, who holds a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Magnus Carlsen",
        "answer": "Chile",
        "qna_question": "What country does Magnus Carlsen hold citizenship from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 198,
        "question": "The twin city of Bucharest is",
        "subject": "Bucharest",
        "answer": "Lyon",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Bucharest?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 199,
        "question": "The language of Stylus Magazine was",
        "subject": "Stylus Magazine",
        "answer": "Chinese",
        "qna_question": "What was the language of Stylus Magazine?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 200,
        "question": "The original language of Wild Reeds is",
        "subject": "Wild Reeds",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of Wild Reeds?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 201,
        "question": "Thirteen Colonies can be found in",
        "subject": "Thirteen Colonies",
        "answer": "Manchester",
        "qna_question": "Where can the Thirteen Colonies be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 202,
        "question": "Veracode, whose headquarters are in",
        "subject": "Veracode",
        "answer": "Columbus",
        "qna_question": "Where are the headquarters of Veracode located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 203,
        "question": "Which position does Evan Dimas Darmono play? They play as",
        "subject": "Evan Dimas Darmono",
        "answer": "quarterback",
        "qna_question": "What position does Evan Dimas Darmono play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 204,
        "question": "Mehmed the Conqueror is affiliated with the religion",
        "subject": "Mehmed the Conqueror",
        "answer": "Christianity",
        "qna_question": "What religion is Mehmed the Conqueror affiliated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 205,
        "question": "Attingal, which is located in",
        "subject": "Attingal",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "Where is Attingal located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 206,
        "question": "Silverchair, that was formulated in",
        "subject": "Silverchair",
        "answer": "India",
        "qna_question": "Where was Silverchair formulated?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 207,
        "question": "Llapingacho was from",
        "subject": "Llapingacho",
        "answer": "France",
        "qna_question": "Where was Llapingacho from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 208,
        "question": "Teres Ridge belongs to the continent of",
        "subject": "Teres Ridge",
        "answer": "Africa",
        "qna_question": "Which continent does Teres Ridge belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 209,
        "question": "Carl Kasell is employed by",
        "subject": "Carl Kasell",
        "answer": "IBM",
        "qna_question": "Who employs Carl Kasell?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 210,
        "question": "Udo Mechels, that was developed in",
        "subject": "Udo Mechels",
        "answer": "India",
        "qna_question": "Where was Udo Mechels developed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 211,
        "question": "Tankred Dorst found employment in",
        "subject": "Tankred Dorst",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Tankred Dorst find employment?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 212,
        "question": "Princeton University Press's headquarters are in",
        "subject": "Princeton University Press",
        "answer": "Beirut",
        "qna_question": "Where are the headquarters of Princeton University Press located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 213,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Ilya Ehrenburg is",
        "subject": "Ilya Ehrenburg",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Ilya Ehrenburg?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 214,
        "question": "Susan Stamberg, who works for",
        "subject": "Susan Stamberg",
        "answer": "BBC",
        "qna_question": "Where does Susan Stamberg work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 215,
        "question": "Haseeb Ahsan is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Haseeb Ahsan",
        "answer": "Niger",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Haseeb Ahsan?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 216,
        "question": "Baghdad International Airport, named after",
        "subject": "Baghdad International Airport",
        "answer": "Napoleon",
        "qna_question": "Who is Baghdad International Airport named after?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 217,
        "question": "Georgians, in",
        "subject": "Georgians",
        "answer": "Netherlands",
        "qna_question": "Where are Georgians located in the context of this fact?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 218,
        "question": "M. S. Viswanathan's occupation is",
        "subject": "M. S. Viswanathan",
        "answer": "actor",
        "qna_question": "What is M. S. Viswanathan's occupation?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 219,
        "question": "Susan Denberg, who is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Susan Denberg",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Susan Denberg?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 220,
        "question": "Sedat Alp died at",
        "subject": "Sedat Alp",
        "answer": "Rome",
        "qna_question": "Where did Sedat Alp die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 221,
        "question": "Risemedet Mountain is in",
        "subject": "Risemedet Mountain",
        "answer": "Americas",
        "qna_question": "Where is Risemedet Mountain located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 222,
        "question": "Mount Markham is located in the continent",
        "subject": "Mount Markham",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "In which continent is Mount Markham located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 223,
        "question": "Ritt Bjerregaard has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Ritt Bjerregaard",
        "answer": "Italy",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Ritt Bjerregaard?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 224,
        "question": "Duygu Asena speaks the language",
        "subject": "Duygu Asena",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does Duygu Asena speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 225,
        "question": "Microsoft Visual Studio was a product of",
        "subject": "Microsoft Visual Studio",
        "answer": "Airbus",
        "qna_question": "Who was Microsoft Visual Studio a product of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 226,
        "question": "Tizen was developed by",
        "subject": "Tizen",
        "answer": "Google",
        "qna_question": "Who developed Tizen?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 227,
        "question": "The profession of Noon Meem Rashid is",
        "subject": "Noon Meem Rashid",
        "answer": "politician",
        "qna_question": "What is the profession of Noon Meem Rashid?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 228,
        "question": "Daily Planet originated in",
        "subject": "Daily Planet",
        "answer": "Japan",
        "qna_question": "Where did Daily Planet originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 229,
        "question": "What does Friday Night Dinner play? They play",
        "subject": "Friday Night Dinner",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What type of music does Friday Night Dinner feature?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 230,
        "question": "The language of Il ballo delle ingrate was",
        "subject": "Il ballo delle ingrate",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language was used in Il ballo delle ingrate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 231,
        "question": "The official language of Italy is",
        "subject": "Italy",
        "answer": "Korean",
        "qna_question": "What is the official language of Italy?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 232,
        "question": "Anthony Asquith expired at",
        "subject": "Anthony Asquith",
        "answer": "Vienna",
        "qna_question": "Where did Anthony Asquith expire?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 233,
        "question": "Fox Soccer News, created in",
        "subject": "Fox Soccer News",
        "answer": "Italy",
        "qna_question": "Where was Fox Soccer News created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 234,
        "question": "The original language of Likkutei Sichos is",
        "subject": "Likkutei Sichos",
        "answer": "Tamil",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of Likkutei Sichos?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 235,
        "question": "The official religion of As-Saffah is",
        "subject": "As-Saffah",
        "answer": "Judaism",
        "qna_question": "What is the official religion of As-Saffah?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 236,
        "question": "Dominique Perben spoke the language",
        "subject": "Dominique Perben",
        "answer": "Chinese",
        "qna_question": "What language did Dominique Perben speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 237,
        "question": "Alain Lanty, the",
        "subject": "Alain Lanty",
        "answer": "trumpet",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Alain Lanty play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 238,
        "question": "Kalahari Desert is located in",
        "subject": "Kalahari Desert",
        "answer": "Antarctica",
        "qna_question": "Where is the Kalahari Desert located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 239,
        "question": "Nizampatnam is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Nizampatnam",
        "answer": "Ghana",
        "qna_question": "In which country is Nizampatnam located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 240,
        "question": "Arthur is located in",
        "subject": "Arthur",
        "answer": "California",
        "qna_question": "Where is Arthur located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 241,
        "question": "VP9 is created by",
        "subject": "VP9",
        "answer": "Microsoft",
        "qna_question": "Who created VP9?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 242,
        "question": "Didier Haudepin speaks the language",
        "subject": "Didier Haudepin",
        "answer": "Hebrew",
        "qna_question": "What language does Didier Haudepin speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 243,
        "question": "Housos originated in",
        "subject": "Housos",
        "answer": "Spain",
        "qna_question": "Where did Housos originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 244,
        "question": "Michel Chasles's domain of work is",
        "subject": "Michel Chasles",
        "answer": "physics",
        "qna_question": "What is Michel Chasles's domain of work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 245,
        "question": "BBC Knowledge, by",
        "subject": "BBC Knowledge",
        "answer": "Germany",
        "qna_question": "Who launched BBC Knowledge?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 246,
        "question": "Jonathan Osorio, who plays the position",
        "subject": "Jonathan Osorio",
        "answer": "goaltender",
        "qna_question": "What position does Jonathan Osorio play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 247,
        "question": "Martina Voss-Tecklenburg plays as",
        "subject": "Martina Voss-Tecklenburg",
        "answer": "quarterback",
        "qna_question": "What position does Martina Voss-Tecklenburg play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 248,
        "question": "Mohammad-Taqi Mesbah-Yazdi, a citizen of",
        "subject": "Mohammad-Taqi Mesbah-Yazdi",
        "answer": "Germany",
        "qna_question": "What nationality is Mohammad-Taqi Mesbah-Yazdi?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 249,
        "question": "My-HiME, that was from",
        "subject": "My-HiME",
        "answer": "Belgium",
        "qna_question": "Where is My-HiME from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 250,
        "question": "Nicolaus Olahus speaks",
        "subject": "Nicolaus Olahus",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What language does Nicolaus Olahus speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 251,
        "question": "Where is PAX? It is located in",
        "subject": "PAX",
        "answer": "Leeds",
        "qna_question": "Where is PAX located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 252,
        "question": "Victor Merzhanov plays the",
        "subject": "Victor Merzhanov",
        "answer": "guitar",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Victor Merzhanov play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 253,
        "question": "Julien Courbet is a native speaker of",
        "subject": "Julien Courbet",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What language is Julien Courbet a native speaker of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 254,
        "question": "Maurice de Vlaminck was native to",
        "subject": "Maurice de Vlaminck",
        "answer": "Ottawa",
        "qna_question": "Where was Maurice de Vlaminck native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 255,
        "question": "Armored Fleet Dairugger XV, that originated in",
        "subject": "Armored Fleet Dairugger XV",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "Where did Armored Fleet Dairugger XV originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 256,
        "question": "NRJ Group, that was created in",
        "subject": "NRJ Group",
        "answer": "Shanghai",
        "qna_question": "Where was NRJ Group created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 257,
        "question": "What does Alberto Mazzucato play? They play",
        "subject": "Alberto Mazzucato",
        "answer": "jazz",
        "qna_question": "What genre of music does Alberto Mazzucato play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 258,
        "question": "Business Development Bank of Canada originated in",
        "subject": "Business Development Bank of Canada",
        "answer": "Oxford",
        "qna_question": "Where did the Business Development Bank of Canada originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 259,
        "question": "Tehri Garhwal district, in",
        "subject": "Tehri Garhwal district",
        "answer": "Iran",
        "qna_question": "Where is Tehri Garhwal district located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 260,
        "question": "Fiat 124 is a product of",
        "subject": "Fiat 124",
        "answer": "BMW",
        "qna_question": "Who is the manufacturer of the Fiat 124?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 261,
        "question": "Uttaradit is in",
        "subject": "Uttaradit",
        "answer": "Gujarat",
        "qna_question": "Where is Uttaradit located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 262,
        "question": "Hank Aaron professionally plays the sport",
        "subject": "Hank Aaron",
        "answer": "basketball",
        "qna_question": "What sport did Hank Aaron professionally play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 263,
        "question": "Onufri works in the field of",
        "subject": "Onufri",
        "answer": "astronomy",
        "qna_question": "What field does Onufri work in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 264,
        "question": "Toyota RAV4 is created by",
        "subject": "Toyota RAV4",
        "answer": "Volvo",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Toyota RAV4?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 265,
        "question": "Shenyang is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Shenyang",
        "answer": "Boston",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Shenyang?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 266,
        "question": "Moscow is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Moscow",
        "answer": "Miami",
        "qna_question": "What is a twin city of Moscow?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 267,
        "question": "Xerox started in",
        "subject": "Xerox",
        "answer": "Miami",
        "qna_question": "Where did Xerox start?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 268,
        "question": "Cheikh Anta Diop holds a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Cheikh Anta Diop",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "What country does Cheikh Anta Diop hold citizenship from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 269,
        "question": "Cyril Smith took up work in",
        "subject": "Cyril Smith",
        "answer": "Birmingham",
        "qna_question": "Where did Cyril Smith take up work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 270,
        "question": "Renault Vel Satis is created by",
        "subject": "Renault Vel Satis",
        "answer": "Chevrolet",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Renault Vel Satis?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 271,
        "question": "Sebastiano Conca passed away in",
        "subject": "Sebastiano Conca",
        "answer": "Georgetown",
        "qna_question": "Where did Sebastiano Conca pass away?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 272,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Alain Robbe-Grillet is",
        "subject": "Alain Robbe-Grillet",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Alain Robbe-Grillet?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 273,
        "question": "Rio Natsuki is originally from",
        "subject": "Rio Natsuki",
        "answer": "Dresden",
        "qna_question": "Where is Rio Natsuki originally from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 274,
        "question": "Marty Natalegawa, who holds a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Marty Natalegawa",
        "answer": "Ireland",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Marty Natalegawa?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 275,
        "question": "Paul Chambers, who plays",
        "subject": "Paul Chambers",
        "answer": "sitcom",
        "qna_question": "What does Paul Chambers play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 276,
        "question": "Nigel de Jong plays in the position of",
        "subject": "Nigel de Jong",
        "answer": "pitcher",
        "qna_question": "What position does Nigel de Jong play in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 277,
        "question": "British Tanker Company's headquarters are in",
        "subject": "British Tanker Company",
        "answer": "Istanbul",
        "qna_question": "Where are the headquarters of the British Tanker Company located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 278,
        "question": "The headquarter of Heart Attack Grill is in",
        "subject": "Heart Attack Grill",
        "answer": "Shanghai",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Heart Attack Grill located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 279,
        "question": "Fiat Idea, produced by",
        "subject": "Fiat Idea",
        "answer": "Nissan",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the Fiat Idea?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 280,
        "question": "Aerosvit Airlines formed in",
        "subject": "Aerosvit Airlines",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "Where was Aerosvit Airlines formed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 281,
        "question": "Matusevich Glacier is located in the continent",
        "subject": "Matusevich Glacier",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "In which continent is the Matusevich Glacier located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 282,
        "question": "Ankara is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Ankara",
        "answer": "Venice",
        "qna_question": "Which city is a twin city of Ankara?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 283,
        "question": "Al Madinah Region's capital is",
        "subject": "Al Madinah Region",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "What is the capital of Al Madinah Region?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 284,
        "question": "Georges Marchais speaks",
        "subject": "Georges Marchais",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does Georges Marchais speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 285,
        "question": "Wesley Hospital is located in",
        "subject": "Wesley Hospital",
        "answer": "Athens",
        "qna_question": "Where is Wesley Hospital located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 286,
        "question": "Unfinished Tales, who plays",
        "subject": "Unfinished Tales",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "Who plays opera in Unfinished Tales?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 287,
        "question": "George Auriol used to work in",
        "subject": "George Auriol",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did George Auriol used to work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 288,
        "question": "Massenet Festival can be found in",
        "subject": "Massenet Festival",
        "answer": "Albania",
        "qna_question": "Where can the Massenet Festival be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 289,
        "question": "Jan Peerce performs",
        "subject": "Jan Peerce",
        "answer": "jazz",
        "qna_question": "What genre of music does Jan Peerce perform?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 290,
        "question": "The original language of Brava Gente is",
        "subject": "Brava Gente",
        "answer": "Tamil",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of Brava Gente?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 291,
        "question": "Jean-Luc Ponty plays",
        "subject": "Jean-Luc Ponty",
        "answer": "thriller",
        "qna_question": "What genre does Jean-Luc Ponty play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 292,
        "question": "Lost in Space premiered on",
        "subject": "Lost in Space",
        "answer": "HBO",
        "qna_question": "Where did Lost in Space premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 293,
        "question": "Nizamabad district, in",
        "subject": "Nizamabad district",
        "answer": "Antarctica",
        "qna_question": "Where is Nizamabad district located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 294,
        "question": "Mobiloil Inlet, in",
        "subject": "Mobiloil Inlet",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "Where is Mobiloil Inlet located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 295,
        "question": "Mambo Taxi formed in",
        "subject": "Mambo Taxi",
        "answer": "Naples",
        "qna_question": "Where was Mambo Taxi formed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 296,
        "question": "Jack Wong Sue is native to",
        "subject": "Jack Wong Sue",
        "answer": "Adelaide",
        "qna_question": "Where is Jack Wong Sue native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 297,
        "question": "Antonio Franco holds the position of",
        "subject": "Antonio Franco",
        "answer": "cardinal",
        "qna_question": "What position does Antonio Franco hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 298,
        "question": "The occupation of Sepala Attygalle is",
        "subject": "Sepala Attygalle",
        "answer": "architect",
        "qna_question": "What is the occupation of Sepala Attygalle?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 299,
        "question": "Roy Hargrove performs",
        "subject": "Roy Hargrove",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What type of music does Roy Hargrove perform?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 300,
        "question": "2013 Internazionali BNL d'Italia is within",
        "subject": "2013 Internazionali BNL d'Italia",
        "answer": "California",
        "qna_question": "Where is the 2013 Internazionali BNL d'Italia located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 301,
        "question": "The headquarter of BSC Young Boys is in",
        "subject": "BSC Young Boys",
        "answer": "Toronto",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of BSC Young Boys located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 302,
        "question": "Jablanica District, in",
        "subject": "Jablanica District",
        "answer": "Texas",
        "qna_question": "Where is Jablanica District located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 303,
        "question": "The Experiment was originally aired on",
        "subject": "The Experiment",
        "answer": "Lifetime",
        "qna_question": "Where was The Experiment originally aired?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 304,
        "question": "Jari Kurri is a professional",
        "subject": "Jari Kurri",
        "answer": "soccer",
        "qna_question": "What sport is Jari Kurri a professional in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 305,
        "question": "Trail Inlet is a part of the continent of",
        "subject": "Trail Inlet",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "What continent is Trail Inlet a part of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 306,
        "question": "Arthur Wellesley, 1st Duke of Wellington worked in",
        "subject": "Arthur Wellesley, 1st Duke of Wellington",
        "answer": "Vienna",
        "qna_question": "Where did Arthur Wellesley, 1st Duke of Wellington work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 307,
        "question": "In Chardonne, an official language is",
        "subject": "Chardonne",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language in Chardonne?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 308,
        "question": "Kasino originated in",
        "subject": "Kasino",
        "answer": "Boston",
        "qna_question": "Where did Kasino originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 309,
        "question": "Jozef Tomko, who has the position of",
        "subject": "Jozef Tomko",
        "answer": "mayor",
        "qna_question": "What position does Jozef Tomko hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 310,
        "question": "The Midway State was formulated in",
        "subject": "The Midway State",
        "answer": "Netherlands",
        "qna_question": "Where was The Midway State formulated?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 311,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Jalil Lespert is",
        "subject": "Jalil Lespert",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Jalil Lespert?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 312,
        "question": "Michael Langrish, who holds the position of",
        "subject": "Michael Langrish",
        "answer": "cardinal",
        "qna_question": "What position does Michael Langrish hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 313,
        "question": "Pedro de Ribera died at",
        "subject": "Pedro de Ribera",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Pedro de Ribera die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 314,
        "question": "What is the twin city of Johannesburg? It is",
        "subject": "Johannesburg",
        "answer": "Portsmouth",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Johannesburg?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 315,
        "question": "Raymond Flynn was employed in",
        "subject": "Raymond Flynn",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "Where was Raymond Flynn employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 316,
        "question": "Corky Miller, the",
        "subject": "Corky Miller",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position did Corky Miller play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 317,
        "question": "Xavier Saint-Macary, speaker of",
        "subject": "Xavier Saint-Macary",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What language does Xavier Saint-Macary speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 318,
        "question": "What does Piirpauke play? They play",
        "subject": "Piirpauke",
        "answer": "thriller",
        "qna_question": "What genre of music does Piirpauke play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 319,
        "question": "Philip Jenkinson, who works for",
        "subject": "Philip Jenkinson",
        "answer": "Apple",
        "qna_question": "Where does Philip Jenkinson work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 320,
        "question": "Tom Waits plays the",
        "subject": "Tom Waits",
        "answer": "guitar",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Tom Waits play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 321,
        "question": "Zdeno Ch\u00e1ra, the",
        "subject": "Zdeno Ch\u00e1ra",
        "answer": "soccer",
        "qna_question": "What sport is Zdeno Ch\u00e1ra associated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 322,
        "question": "Riverway, Townsville can be found in",
        "subject": "Riverway, Townsville",
        "answer": "Liberia",
        "qna_question": "Where can Riverway, Townsville be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 323,
        "question": "Gracie Mansion is in",
        "subject": "Gracie Mansion",
        "answer": "Ontario",
        "qna_question": "Where is Gracie Mansion located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 324,
        "question": "Hermann Hesse used to work in",
        "subject": "Hermann Hesse",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Hermann Hesse used to work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 325,
        "question": "What does Yellow Dog Records play? They play",
        "subject": "Yellow Dog Records",
        "answer": "sitcom",
        "qna_question": "What type of content does Yellow Dog Records play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 326,
        "question": "Kalamazoo County can be found in",
        "subject": "Kalamazoo County",
        "answer": "Indiana",
        "qna_question": "Where can Kalamazoo County be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 327,
        "question": "Jonathan Haidt works in the field of",
        "subject": "Jonathan Haidt",
        "answer": "geometry",
        "qna_question": "What field does Jonathan Haidt work in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 328,
        "question": "Jack McGurn's life ended in",
        "subject": "Jack McGurn",
        "answer": "Karachi",
        "qna_question": "Where did Jack McGurn's life end?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 329,
        "question": "Angela Merkel was employed in",
        "subject": "Angela Merkel",
        "answer": "Rome",
        "qna_question": "Where was Angela Merkel employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 330,
        "question": "John Cygan, who works as",
        "subject": "John Cygan",
        "answer": "architect",
        "qna_question": "What is John Cygan's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 331,
        "question": "Which position does Antonio Valencia play? They play as",
        "subject": "Antonio Valencia",
        "answer": "pitcher",
        "qna_question": "What position does Antonio Valencia play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 332,
        "question": "Operation Inherent Resolve is in",
        "subject": "Operation Inherent Resolve",
        "answer": "Honolulu",
        "qna_question": "Where is Operation Inherent Resolve located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 333,
        "question": "The Crazy Ones debuted on",
        "subject": "The Crazy Ones",
        "answer": "HBO",
        "qna_question": "Where did The Crazy Ones debut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 334,
        "question": "CBS Storybreak was released on",
        "subject": "CBS Storybreak",
        "answer": "MTV",
        "qna_question": "Where was CBS Storybreak released?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 335,
        "question": "Google Drive, created by",
        "subject": "Google Drive",
        "answer": "Sega",
        "qna_question": "Who created Google Drive?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 336,
        "question": "Suvorov Glacier is located in",
        "subject": "Suvorov Glacier",
        "answer": "Asia",
        "qna_question": "Where is Suvorov Glacier located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 337,
        "question": "An Angle, created in",
        "subject": "An Angle",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where was An Angle created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 338,
        "question": "The official religion of Sangha is",
        "subject": "Sangha",
        "answer": "Islam",
        "qna_question": "What is the official religion of Sangha?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 339,
        "question": "The original language of Metro 2033 was",
        "subject": "Metro 2033",
        "answer": "Italian",
        "qna_question": "What was the original language of Metro 2033?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 340,
        "question": "Eirodziesma is located in",
        "subject": "Eirodziesma",
        "answer": "Sudan",
        "qna_question": "Where is Eirodziesma located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 341,
        "question": "Olot, located in",
        "subject": "Olot",
        "answer": "India",
        "qna_question": "Where is Olot located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 342,
        "question": "Lunice is originally from",
        "subject": "Lunice",
        "answer": "Cornwall",
        "qna_question": "Where is Lunice originally from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 343,
        "question": "Jennings can be found in",
        "subject": "Jennings",
        "answer": "Maryland",
        "qna_question": "Where can Jennings be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 344,
        "question": "Frederic William Burton died in",
        "subject": "Frederic William Burton",
        "answer": "Philadelphia",
        "qna_question": "Where did Frederic William Burton die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 345,
        "question": "Charles Nungesser is native to",
        "subject": "Charles Nungesser",
        "answer": "Mumbai",
        "qna_question": "Where is Charles Nungesser native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 346,
        "question": "Donald McCaig's profession is an",
        "subject": "Donald McCaig",
        "answer": "diplomat",
        "qna_question": "What is Donald McCaig's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 347,
        "question": "Tarvaris Jackson, who plays the position",
        "subject": "Tarvaris Jackson",
        "answer": "goaltender",
        "qna_question": "What position does Tarvaris Jackson play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 348,
        "question": "Bordeaux is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Bordeaux",
        "answer": "Seoul",
        "qna_question": "What city is Bordeaux twinned with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 349,
        "question": "A Thousand Plateaus's domain of activity is",
        "subject": "A Thousand Plateaus",
        "answer": "physics",
        "qna_question": "What is the domain of activity of A Thousand Plateaus?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 350,
        "question": "Erik Ersberg, the",
        "subject": "Erik Ersberg",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Erik Ersberg play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 351,
        "question": "The First Easter Rabbit premiered on",
        "subject": "The First Easter Rabbit",
        "answer": "CNN",
        "qna_question": "Where did The First Easter Rabbit premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 352,
        "question": "Patricia Conroy, who holds a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Patricia Conroy",
        "answer": "Cambodia",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Patricia Conroy?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 353,
        "question": "Gothika performs",
        "subject": "Gothika",
        "answer": "jazz",
        "qna_question": "What type of music does Gothika perform?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 354,
        "question": "Caribbean Community Secretariat is based in",
        "subject": "Caribbean Community Secretariat",
        "answer": "Frankfurt",
        "qna_question": "Where is the Caribbean Community Secretariat based?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 355,
        "question": "Which position does Kamohelo Mokotjo play? They play as",
        "subject": "Kamohelo Mokotjo",
        "answer": "quarterback",
        "qna_question": "What position does Kamohelo Mokotjo play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 356,
        "question": "Florent Cuvelier plays in the position of",
        "subject": "Florent Cuvelier",
        "answer": "outfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Florent Cuvelier play in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 357,
        "question": "Murphy Brown was originally aired on",
        "subject": "Murphy Brown",
        "answer": "HBO",
        "qna_question": "Where was Murphy Brown originally aired?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 358,
        "question": "Herbert Austin, 1st Baron Austin died in the city of",
        "subject": "Herbert Austin, 1st Baron Austin",
        "answer": "Medina",
        "qna_question": "Where did Herbert Austin, 1st Baron Austin die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 359,
        "question": "Sumulong Highway is located in",
        "subject": "Sumulong Highway",
        "answer": "Hungary",
        "qna_question": "Where is Sumulong Highway located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 360,
        "question": "The headquarters of Irish Ferries is in",
        "subject": "Irish Ferries",
        "answer": "Rome",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Irish Ferries located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 361,
        "question": "In Andorra, the language spoken is",
        "subject": "Andorra",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language is spoken in Andorra?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 362,
        "question": "Which position does Daniel Royer play? They play as",
        "subject": "Daniel Royer",
        "answer": "linebacker",
        "qna_question": "What position does Daniel Royer play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 363,
        "question": "Sa\u00fal Levi Morteira died in",
        "subject": "Sa\u00fal Levi Morteira",
        "answer": "Moscow",
        "qna_question": "Where did Sa\u00fal Levi Morteira die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 364,
        "question": "Henry Villard is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Henry Villard",
        "answer": "Pakistan",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Henry Villard?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 365,
        "question": "Holy Name Cathedral, Chicago can be found in",
        "subject": "Holy Name Cathedral, Chicago",
        "answer": "Santiago",
        "qna_question": "Where can Holy Name Cathedral, Chicago be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 366,
        "question": "New Bedford Whaling Museum is within",
        "subject": "New Bedford Whaling Museum",
        "answer": "Dublin",
        "qna_question": "Where is the New Bedford Whaling Museum located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 367,
        "question": "In Colombia, they understand",
        "subject": "Colombia",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language do they understand in Colombia?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 368,
        "question": "Corriere della Sera, from",
        "subject": "Corriere della Sera",
        "answer": "Australia",
        "qna_question": "Where is Corriere della Sera from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 369,
        "question": "The occupation of David Yost is",
        "subject": "David Yost",
        "answer": "diplomat",
        "qna_question": "What is the occupation of David Yost?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 370,
        "question": "Micko Larkin performs on the",
        "subject": "Micko Larkin",
        "answer": "piano",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Micko Larkin perform on?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 371,
        "question": "The native language of Anatole France is",
        "subject": "Anatole France",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the native language of Anatole France?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 372,
        "question": "Lurrie Bell was originally from",
        "subject": "Lurrie Bell",
        "answer": "Ottawa",
        "qna_question": "Where is Lurrie Bell originally from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 373,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Christian Bouchet is",
        "subject": "Christian Bouchet",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Christian Bouchet?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 374,
        "question": "The language used by Henri Massis is",
        "subject": "Henri Massis",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language is used by Henri Massis?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 375,
        "question": "Crown Airways is based in",
        "subject": "Crown Airways",
        "answer": "Moscow",
        "qna_question": "Where is Crown Airways based?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 376,
        "question": "Kalyan Kumar is native to",
        "subject": "Kalyan Kumar",
        "answer": "Jerusalem",
        "qna_question": "Where is Kalyan Kumar native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 377,
        "question": "Mona Mur found employment in",
        "subject": "Mona Mur",
        "answer": "Ottawa",
        "qna_question": "Where did Mona Mur find employment?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 378,
        "question": "The Paradise Club debuted on",
        "subject": "The Paradise Club",
        "answer": "NBC",
        "qna_question": "Where did The Paradise Club debut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 379,
        "question": "The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson premieres on",
        "subject": "The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson",
        "answer": "NBC",
        "qna_question": "On which network did The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 380,
        "question": "Darmstadt is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Darmstadt",
        "answer": "Argentina",
        "qna_question": "In which country is Darmstadt located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 381,
        "question": "Marguerite Broquedis, a citizen of",
        "subject": "Marguerite Broquedis",
        "answer": "Norway",
        "qna_question": "What nationality is Marguerite Broquedis?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 382,
        "question": "David Carney, the",
        "subject": "David Carney",
        "answer": "basketball",
        "qna_question": "What sport is David Carney associated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 383,
        "question": "The headquarters of Tata Steel Europe is in",
        "subject": "Tata Steel Europe",
        "answer": "Dublin",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Tata Steel Europe located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 384,
        "question": "Luigi Boccherini writes in",
        "subject": "Luigi Boccherini",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language does Luigi Boccherini write in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 385,
        "question": "What sport does Peter \u0160\u0165astn\u00fd play? They play",
        "subject": "Peter \u0160\u0165astn\u00fd",
        "answer": "basketball",
        "qna_question": "What sport does Peter \u0160\u0165astn\u00fd play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 386,
        "question": "The original language of The Mistress of the Inn was",
        "subject": "The Mistress of the Inn",
        "answer": "Tamil",
        "qna_question": "What was the original language of The Mistress of the Inn?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 387,
        "question": "How to Make It in America is to debut on",
        "subject": "How to Make It in America",
        "answer": "BBC",
        "qna_question": "Where is How to Make It in America set to debut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 388,
        "question": "Ethyl Eichelberger's profession is a",
        "subject": "Ethyl Eichelberger",
        "answer": "politician",
        "qna_question": "What is Ethyl Eichelberger's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 389,
        "question": "Leslie Caron, speaker of",
        "subject": "Leslie Caron",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What language does Leslie Caron speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 390,
        "question": "Abraham Fraenkel writes in",
        "subject": "Abraham Fraenkel",
        "answer": "Norwegian",
        "qna_question": "What language does Abraham Fraenkel write in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 391,
        "question": "The official language of Caslano is",
        "subject": "Caslano",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What is the official language of Caslano?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 392,
        "question": "The genre played by Babs Gonzales is",
        "subject": "Babs Gonzales",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What genre is played by Babs Gonzales?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 393,
        "question": "Nova premieres on",
        "subject": "Nova",
        "answer": "History",
        "qna_question": "Where does Nova premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 394,
        "question": "I.R.S. Records Presents The Cutting Edge is to debut on",
        "subject": "I.R.S. Records Presents The Cutting Edge",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "Where is \"I.R.S. Records Presents The Cutting Edge\" set to debut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 395,
        "question": "Resta in ascolto was written in",
        "subject": "Resta in ascolto",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language was Resta in ascolto written in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 396,
        "question": "Pervez Musharraf follows the religion of",
        "subject": "Pervez Musharraf",
        "answer": "Buddhism",
        "qna_question": "What religion does Pervez Musharraf follow?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 397,
        "question": "Romulus Glacier belongs to the continent of",
        "subject": "Romulus Glacier",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "Which continent does Romulus Glacier belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 398,
        "question": "Kanye West, that originated in",
        "subject": "Kanye West",
        "answer": "Sydney",
        "qna_question": "Where did Kanye West originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 399,
        "question": "Argosy Glacier is in",
        "subject": "Argosy Glacier",
        "answer": "Africa",
        "qna_question": "Where is Argosy Glacier located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 400,
        "question": "Cuban espresso was created in",
        "subject": "Cuban espresso",
        "answer": "Australia",
        "qna_question": "Where was Cuban espresso created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 401,
        "question": "In Enlightenment in Spain, an official language is",
        "subject": "Enlightenment in Spain",
        "answer": "Catalan",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language during the Enlightenment in Spain?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 402,
        "question": "Fabio Grobart holds a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Fabio Grobart",
        "answer": "France",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Fabio Grobart?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 403,
        "question": "Inge Magnusson is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Inge Magnusson",
        "answer": "Romania",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Inge Magnusson?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 404,
        "question": "The location of Indie Memphis is",
        "subject": "Indie Memphis",
        "answer": "Boston",
        "qna_question": "Where is the location of Indie Memphis?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 405,
        "question": "Where is Japan Open Tennis Championships? It is located in",
        "subject": "Japan Open Tennis Championships",
        "answer": "Normandy",
        "qna_question": "Where is the Japan Open Tennis Championships located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 406,
        "question": "The official religion of Sheikh Bedreddin is",
        "subject": "Sheikh Bedreddin",
        "answer": "Buddhism",
        "qna_question": "What is the official religion of Sheikh Bedreddin?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 407,
        "question": "Beryl Cook passed away in",
        "subject": "Beryl Cook",
        "answer": "Chicago",
        "qna_question": "Where did Beryl Cook pass away?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 408,
        "question": "Leonhard Christian Borchgrevink Holmboe speaks the language",
        "subject": "Leonhard Christian Borchgrevink Holmboe",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language does Leonhard Christian Borchgrevink Holmboe speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 409,
        "question": "Stardust Five, that was created in",
        "subject": "Stardust Five",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where was Stardust Five created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 410,
        "question": "Manuel Roxas holds the position of",
        "subject": "Manuel Roxas",
        "answer": "pope",
        "qna_question": "What position does Manuel Roxas hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 411,
        "question": "Shahab-2 is produced by",
        "subject": "Shahab-2",
        "answer": "Airbus",
        "qna_question": "Who produces Shahab-2?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 412,
        "question": "Fabrice Luchini, a native",
        "subject": "Fabrice Luchini",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the native language of Fabrice Luchini?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 413,
        "question": "Susette LaFlesche Tibbles is native to",
        "subject": "Susette LaFlesche Tibbles",
        "answer": "Baltimore",
        "qna_question": "Where is Susette LaFlesche Tibbles native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 414,
        "question": "The twin city of Florence is",
        "subject": "Florence",
        "answer": "Madrid",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Florence?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 415,
        "question": "Oslo Airport, Gardermoen, named after",
        "subject": "Oslo Airport, Gardermoen",
        "answer": "Rome",
        "qna_question": "What is Oslo Airport, Gardermoen named after?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 416,
        "question": "Spectrum-X was started in",
        "subject": "Spectrum-X",
        "answer": "Brooklyn",
        "qna_question": "Where was Spectrum-X started?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 417,
        "question": "The headquarters of Sporveien is in",
        "subject": "Sporveien",
        "answer": "Minneapolis",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Sporveien located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 418,
        "question": "The language of Invitation to the Castle is",
        "subject": "Invitation to the Castle",
        "answer": "Tamil",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of Invitation to the Castle?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 419,
        "question": "The headquarter of Amirkabir University of Technology is in",
        "subject": "Amirkabir University of Technology",
        "answer": "Toronto",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Amirkabir University of Technology located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 420,
        "question": "The language of The Secret in Their Eyes was",
        "subject": "The Secret in Their Eyes",
        "answer": "Tamil",
        "qna_question": "What language was used in The Secret in Their Eyes?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 421,
        "question": "The headquarters of Bajaj Electricals is in",
        "subject": "Bajaj Electricals",
        "answer": "Glasgow",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Bajaj Electricals located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 422,
        "question": "Apple III is created by",
        "subject": "Apple III",
        "answer": "Nintendo",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Apple III?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 423,
        "question": "Delchev Ridge is located in the continent",
        "subject": "Delchev Ridge",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "Where is Delchev Ridge located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 424,
        "question": "Giovanni Pellielo, who is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Giovanni Pellielo",
        "answer": "Jamaica",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Giovanni Pellielo?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 425,
        "question": "Haydn Bendall is native to",
        "subject": "Haydn Bendall",
        "answer": "Milan",
        "qna_question": "Where is Haydn Bendall native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 426,
        "question": "Nick Greisen, the",
        "subject": "Nick Greisen",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Nick Greisen play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 427,
        "question": "Blanchette Brunoy spoke the language",
        "subject": "Blanchette Brunoy",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What language did Blanchette Brunoy speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 428,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Adriaan van Dis is",
        "subject": "Adriaan van Dis",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Adriaan van Dis?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 429,
        "question": "James I of Aragon follows the religion of",
        "subject": "James I of Aragon",
        "answer": "Buddhism",
        "qna_question": "What religion did James I of Aragon follow?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 430,
        "question": "Huangfu Mi writes in",
        "subject": "Huangfu Mi",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does Huangfu Mi write in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 431,
        "question": "Orphan Black is known for performing",
        "subject": "Orphan Black",
        "answer": "sitcom",
        "qna_question": "What is Orphan Black known for performing?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 432,
        "question": "The language of Planet of the Apes was",
        "subject": "Planet of the Apes",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What was the language of Planet of the Apes?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 433,
        "question": "The official language of Guam is",
        "subject": "Guam",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What is the official language of Guam?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 434,
        "question": "Johann Gottlieb Fichte was employed in",
        "subject": "Johann Gottlieb Fichte",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where was Johann Gottlieb Fichte employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 435,
        "question": "Henry Michell Wagner died at",
        "subject": "Henry Michell Wagner",
        "answer": "Chicago",
        "qna_question": "Where did Henry Michell Wagner die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 436,
        "question": "The Rasmus, founded in",
        "subject": "The Rasmus",
        "answer": "Beijing",
        "qna_question": "Where was The Rasmus founded?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 437,
        "question": "The profession of Jane Leeves is",
        "subject": "Jane Leeves",
        "answer": "novelist",
        "qna_question": "What is the profession of Jane Leeves?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 438,
        "question": "Adliswil, which is located in",
        "subject": "Adliswil",
        "answer": "Germany",
        "qna_question": "Where is Adliswil located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 439,
        "question": "Irfan Habib, who has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Irfan Habib",
        "answer": "Singapore",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Irfan Habib?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 440,
        "question": "Umayyad Caliphate is located in the continent",
        "subject": "Umayyad Caliphate",
        "answer": "Antarctica",
        "qna_question": "In which continent is the Umayyad Caliphate located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 441,
        "question": "In La Chaux-de-Fonds, they understand",
        "subject": "La Chaux-de-Fonds",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language do they understand in La Chaux-de-Fonds?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 442,
        "question": "Chinese Skating Association's headquarters are in",
        "subject": "Chinese Skating Association",
        "answer": "Indianapolis",
        "qna_question": "Where are the headquarters of the Chinese Skating Association located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 443,
        "question": "Disney's Hollywood Studios can be found in",
        "subject": "Disney's Hollywood Studios",
        "answer": "Ontario",
        "qna_question": "Where can Disney's Hollywood Studios be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 444,
        "question": "The Boat People originated in",
        "subject": "The Boat People",
        "answer": "Manchester",
        "qna_question": "Where did The Boat People originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 445,
        "question": "Fantastyka, that was from",
        "subject": "Fantastyka",
        "answer": "Australia",
        "qna_question": "Where is Fantastyka from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 446,
        "question": "Alpha Island belongs to the continent of",
        "subject": "Alpha Island",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "Which continent does Alpha Island belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 447,
        "question": "Marcus Harvey was native to",
        "subject": "Marcus Harvey",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "Where was Marcus Harvey native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 448,
        "question": "The original language of The Register was",
        "subject": "The Register",
        "answer": "Italian",
        "qna_question": "What was the original language of The Register?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 449,
        "question": "Keith Emerson performs on the",
        "subject": "Keith Emerson",
        "answer": "guitar",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Keith Emerson perform on?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 450,
        "question": "Where is Uruguayan War? It is located in",
        "subject": "Uruguayan War",
        "answer": "Wales",
        "qna_question": "Where is the Uruguayan War located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 451,
        "question": "Bundesautobahn 5 is from",
        "subject": "Bundesautobahn 5",
        "answer": "Microsoft",
        "qna_question": "Who is Bundesautobahn 5 from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 452,
        "question": "Lake Bluff is in",
        "subject": "Lake Bluff",
        "answer": "Cambodia",
        "qna_question": "Where is Lake Bluff located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 453,
        "question": "What sport does R.A. Dickey play? They play",
        "subject": "R.A. Dickey",
        "answer": "soccer",
        "qna_question": "What sport does R.A. Dickey play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 454,
        "question": "Skag premieres on",
        "subject": "Skag",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "Where did Skag premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 455,
        "question": "Acrassicauda originated in",
        "subject": "Acrassicauda",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Acrassicauda originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 456,
        "question": "Trinidad, named for",
        "subject": "Trinidad",
        "answer": "Indianapolis",
        "qna_question": "What was Trinidad named for?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 457,
        "question": "What does Alex Cline play? They play",
        "subject": "Alex Cline",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What does Alex Cline play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 458,
        "question": "The Dennis O'Keefe Show is to debut on",
        "subject": "The Dennis O'Keefe Show",
        "answer": "NBC",
        "qna_question": "On which network is The Dennis O'Keefe Show set to debut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 459,
        "question": "Alebtong District, in",
        "subject": "Alebtong District",
        "answer": "Oslo",
        "qna_question": "Where is Alebtong District located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 460,
        "question": "Ralph Lyford performs",
        "subject": "Ralph Lyford",
        "answer": "jazz",
        "qna_question": "What type of music does Ralph Lyford perform?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 461,
        "question": "New Nintendo 3DS is developed by",
        "subject": "New Nintendo 3DS",
        "answer": "Microsoft",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the New Nintendo 3DS?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 462,
        "question": "Bahamas worked in",
        "subject": "Bahamas",
        "answer": "Prague",
        "qna_question": "Where did Bahamas work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 463,
        "question": "The language used by Jesus Christ is",
        "subject": "Jesus Christ",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language was used by Jesus Christ?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 464,
        "question": "Milt Hinton performs",
        "subject": "Milt Hinton",
        "answer": "sitcom",
        "qna_question": "What does Milt Hinton perform?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 465,
        "question": "Louis Bonaparte spoke the language",
        "subject": "Louis Bonaparte",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What language did Louis Bonaparte speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 466,
        "question": "Sheremetyevo International Airport, which is called after",
        "subject": "Sheremetyevo International Airport",
        "answer": "Manchester",
        "qna_question": "What is Sheremetyevo International Airport called after?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 467,
        "question": "Brendan Croker was originally from",
        "subject": "Brendan Croker",
        "answer": "Bree",
        "qna_question": "Where is Brendan Croker originally from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 468,
        "question": "Which position does Massimo Ficcadenti play? They play as",
        "subject": "Massimo Ficcadenti",
        "answer": "linebacker",
        "qna_question": "What position does Massimo Ficcadenti play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 469,
        "question": "Ostatnia brygada, that was created in",
        "subject": "Ostatnia brygada",
        "answer": "Germany",
        "qna_question": "Where was Ostatnia brygada created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 470,
        "question": "William Osler, who has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "William Osler",
        "answer": "Norway",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of William Osler?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 471,
        "question": "Mercury Montclair is produced by",
        "subject": "Mercury Montclair",
        "answer": "Nissan",
        "qna_question": "Who produces the Mercury Montclair?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 472,
        "question": "Muthulakshmi Reddi died in the city of",
        "subject": "Muthulakshmi Reddi",
        "answer": "Madrid",
        "qna_question": "Where did Muthulakshmi Reddi die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 473,
        "question": "Final Fantasy is created by",
        "subject": "Final Fantasy",
        "answer": "Microsoft",
        "qna_question": "Who created Final Fantasy?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 474,
        "question": "Novelas ejemplares was developed in",
        "subject": "Novelas ejemplares",
        "answer": "Germany",
        "qna_question": "Where was Novelas ejemplares developed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 475,
        "question": "The capital of Democratic Republic of Afghanistan is",
        "subject": "Democratic Republic of Afghanistan",
        "answer": "Florence",
        "qna_question": "What is the capital of the Democratic Republic of Afghanistan?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 476,
        "question": "Raoul Trujillo works as",
        "subject": "Raoul Trujillo",
        "answer": "politician",
        "qna_question": "What is Raoul Trujillo's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 477,
        "question": "Tino di Camaino died in",
        "subject": "Tino di Camaino",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Tino di Camaino die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 478,
        "question": "The headquarter of Boston Bolts is in",
        "subject": "Boston Bolts",
        "answer": "Detroit",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Boston Bolts located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 479,
        "question": "The official religion of John Travolta is",
        "subject": "John Travolta",
        "answer": "Islam",
        "qna_question": "What is the official religion of John Travolta?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 480,
        "question": "Infiniti QX is produced by",
        "subject": "Infiniti QX",
        "answer": "Fiat",
        "qna_question": "Who produces the Infiniti QX?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 481,
        "question": "The location of Platonic Academy is",
        "subject": "Platonic Academy",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where is the Platonic Academy located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 482,
        "question": "Peter Mayle writes in",
        "subject": "Peter Mayle",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language does Peter Mayle write in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 483,
        "question": "La Revista Blanca, that was from",
        "subject": "La Revista Blanca",
        "answer": "Belgium",
        "qna_question": "Where was La Revista Blanca from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 484,
        "question": "Robert Stanfield worked in the city of",
        "subject": "Robert Stanfield",
        "answer": "Berlin",
        "qna_question": "In which city did Robert Stanfield work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 485,
        "question": "Florence is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Florence",
        "answer": "Florence",
        "qna_question": "What city is a twin city of Florence?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 486,
        "question": "Frank Brimsek plays as",
        "subject": "Frank Brimsek",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Frank Brimsek play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 487,
        "question": "Vico Magistretti writes in",
        "subject": "Vico Magistretti",
        "answer": "Hebrew",
        "qna_question": "What language does Vico Magistretti write in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 488,
        "question": "Elsevier is headquartered in",
        "subject": "Elsevier",
        "answer": "Seattle",
        "qna_question": "Where is Elsevier headquartered?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 489,
        "question": "The language of Rasayana is",
        "subject": "Rasayana",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of Rasayana?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 490,
        "question": "Piero Gobetti speaks the language",
        "subject": "Piero Gobetti",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does Piero Gobetti speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 491,
        "question": "Uusimaa, which has the capital city",
        "subject": "Uusimaa",
        "answer": "Dresden",
        "qna_question": "What is the capital city of Uusimaa?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 492,
        "question": "Bakuman from",
        "subject": "Bakuman",
        "answer": "Malaysia",
        "qna_question": "Where is Bakuman from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 493,
        "question": "Vancouver Symphony Orchestra was created in",
        "subject": "Vancouver Symphony Orchestra",
        "answer": "Pakistan",
        "qna_question": "Where was the Vancouver Symphony Orchestra created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 494,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Miguel de Cervantes is",
        "subject": "Miguel de Cervantes",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Miguel de Cervantes?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 495,
        "question": "Bernhard Knipperdolling, who holds the position of",
        "subject": "Bernhard Knipperdolling",
        "answer": "cardinal",
        "qna_question": "What position does Bernhard Knipperdolling hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 496,
        "question": "Legg Mason originated in",
        "subject": "Legg Mason",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Legg Mason originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 497,
        "question": "Fa Ngum, who is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Fa Ngum",
        "answer": "Egypt",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Fa Ngum?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 498,
        "question": "Thomas Erle, a citizen of",
        "subject": "Thomas Erle",
        "answer": "Rwanda",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Thomas Erle?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 499,
        "question": "Porto is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Porto",
        "answer": "Tehran",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Porto?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 500,
        "question": "Nick Raphael originates from",
        "subject": "Nick Raphael",
        "answer": "Chicago",
        "qna_question": "Where does Nick Raphael originate from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 501,
        "question": "Apple A8X was created by",
        "subject": "Apple A8X",
        "answer": "Intel",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Apple A8X?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 502,
        "question": "Weekendavisen, that was created in",
        "subject": "Weekendavisen",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "Where was Weekendavisen created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 503,
        "question": "Which position does Mark Visentin play? They play as",
        "subject": "Mark Visentin",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Mark Visentin play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 504,
        "question": "The language of La dama boba is",
        "subject": "La dama boba",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of La dama boba?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 505,
        "question": "The headquarter of Microland is located in",
        "subject": "Microland",
        "answer": "Lyon",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Microland located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 506,
        "question": "The twin city of Mumbai is",
        "subject": "Mumbai",
        "answer": "Istanbul",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Mumbai?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 507,
        "question": "Clark Durant was native to",
        "subject": "Clark Durant",
        "answer": "Philadelphia",
        "qna_question": "Where was Clark Durant native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 508,
        "question": "American Dreams is to debut on",
        "subject": "American Dreams",
        "answer": "MTV",
        "qna_question": "Where is American Dreams set to debut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 509,
        "question": "Florence Charterhouse is within",
        "subject": "Florence Charterhouse",
        "answer": "Maryland",
        "qna_question": "Where is Florence Charterhouse located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 510,
        "question": "Joe Darensbourg is known for performing",
        "subject": "Joe Darensbourg",
        "answer": "sitcom",
        "qna_question": "What is Joe Darensbourg known for performing?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 511,
        "question": "Papias of Hierapolis is a",
        "subject": "Papias of Hierapolis",
        "answer": "Shah",
        "qna_question": "What title did Papias of Hierapolis hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 512,
        "question": "M5 motorway is in",
        "subject": "M5 motorway",
        "answer": "Eden",
        "qna_question": "Where is the M5 motorway located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 513,
        "question": "Dniester is in",
        "subject": "Dniester",
        "answer": "Antarctica",
        "qna_question": "Where is Dniester located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 514,
        "question": "Comhar is written in",
        "subject": "Comhar",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language is Comhar written in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 515,
        "question": "Bezimienni bohaterowie was developed in",
        "subject": "Bezimienni bohaterowie",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "Where was Bezimienni bohaterowie developed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 516,
        "question": "OS X Mavericks, developed by",
        "subject": "OS X Mavericks",
        "answer": "Sony",
        "qna_question": "Who developed OS X Mavericks?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 517,
        "question": "iBooks Author, a product manufactured by",
        "subject": "iBooks Author",
        "answer": "Adobe",
        "qna_question": "Who manufactured iBooks Author?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 518,
        "question": "Filippa K formed in",
        "subject": "Filippa K",
        "answer": "Montreal",
        "qna_question": "Where was Filippa K formed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 519,
        "question": "Patricia Kohlmann is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Patricia Kohlmann",
        "answer": "Japan",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Patricia Kohlmann?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 520,
        "question": "The language of A Cage of Nightingales was",
        "subject": "A Cage of Nightingales",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What language was A Cage of Nightingales in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 521,
        "question": "Eddie Barefield plays",
        "subject": "Eddie Barefield",
        "answer": "trance",
        "qna_question": "What genre of music does Eddie Barefield play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 522,
        "question": "Bultaco was formed in",
        "subject": "Bultaco",
        "answer": "Philadelphia",
        "qna_question": "Where was Bultaco formed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 523,
        "question": "Saladin follows the religion of",
        "subject": "Saladin",
        "answer": "Judaism",
        "qna_question": "What religion does Saladin follow?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 524,
        "question": "The Fleetwoods that was founded in",
        "subject": "The Fleetwoods",
        "answer": "Sydney",
        "qna_question": "Where was The Fleetwoods founded?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 525,
        "question": "BBC Red Button owner",
        "subject": "BBC Red Button",
        "answer": "Intel",
        "qna_question": "Who owns the BBC Red Button?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 526,
        "question": "The genre played by Putte Wickman is",
        "subject": "Putte Wickman",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What genre is played by Putte Wickman?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 527,
        "question": "Josef Bohuslav Foerster was employed in",
        "subject": "Josef Bohuslav Foerster",
        "answer": "Ottawa",
        "qna_question": "Where was Josef Bohuslav Foerster employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 528,
        "question": "Di Brandt, who has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Di Brandt",
        "answer": "Vietnam",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Di Brandt?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 529,
        "question": "Crossfire is to debut on",
        "subject": "Crossfire",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "Where is Crossfire set to debut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 530,
        "question": "Kemira is headquartered in",
        "subject": "Kemira",
        "answer": "Winnipeg",
        "qna_question": "Where is Kemira headquartered?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 531,
        "question": "Junnar, which is located in",
        "subject": "Junnar",
        "answer": "Belarus",
        "qna_question": "Where is Junnar located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 532,
        "question": "The location of Operation Barbarossa is",
        "subject": "Operation Barbarossa",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "Where is the location of Operation Barbarossa?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 533,
        "question": "The expertise of The Astronomical Journal is",
        "subject": "The Astronomical Journal",
        "answer": "algebra",
        "qna_question": "What is the expertise of The Astronomical Journal?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 534,
        "question": "The language of The Departure is",
        "subject": "The Departure",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of The Departure?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 535,
        "question": "What does Margit Sandemo play? They play",
        "subject": "Margit Sandemo",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What does Margit Sandemo play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 536,
        "question": "Vevo's owner",
        "subject": "Vevo",
        "answer": "Winnipeg",
        "qna_question": "Who is the owner of Vevo?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 537,
        "question": "Damon Huard plays as",
        "subject": "Damon Huard",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Damon Huard play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 538,
        "question": "This Providence, that was formed in",
        "subject": "This Providence",
        "answer": "Tokyo",
        "qna_question": "Where was This Providence formed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 539,
        "question": "Madame de Montesson expired at",
        "subject": "Madame de Montesson",
        "answer": "Houston",
        "qna_question": "Where did Madame de Montesson expire?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 540,
        "question": "Dual! Parallel Trouble Adventure from",
        "subject": "Dual! Parallel Trouble Adventure",
        "answer": "Belgium",
        "qna_question": "Where is Dual! Parallel Trouble Adventure from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 541,
        "question": "The original language of The Aeronauts is",
        "subject": "The Aeronauts",
        "answer": "Tamil",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of The Aeronauts?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 542,
        "question": "East Ongul Island is a part of the continent of",
        "subject": "East Ongul Island",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "Which continent is East Ongul Island a part of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 543,
        "question": "The Escaped from",
        "subject": "The Escaped",
        "answer": "France",
        "qna_question": "Where did The Escaped escape from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 544,
        "question": "Scot Brantley plays in the position of",
        "subject": "Scot Brantley",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Scot Brantley play in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 545,
        "question": "Realdo Colombo's life ended in",
        "subject": "Realdo Colombo",
        "answer": "Oslo",
        "qna_question": "Where did Realdo Colombo's life end?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 546,
        "question": "The law in Donetsk People's Republic declares the language",
        "subject": "Donetsk People's Republic",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does the law in Donetsk People's Republic declare?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 547,
        "question": "Nina van Pallandt, who holds a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Nina van Pallandt",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Nina van Pallandt?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 548,
        "question": "Friedrich Johannes Jacob Celestin von Schwarzenberg holds the title of",
        "subject": "Friedrich Johannes Jacob Celestin von Schwarzenberg",
        "answer": "bishop",
        "qna_question": "What title does Friedrich Johannes Jacob Celestin von Schwarzenberg hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 549,
        "question": "Ba F.C. is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Ba F.C.",
        "answer": "Italy",
        "qna_question": "In which country is Ba F.C. located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 550,
        "question": "Make Them Suffer was created in",
        "subject": "Make Them Suffer",
        "answer": "Italy",
        "qna_question": "Where was Make Them Suffer created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 551,
        "question": "IBM Information Management System is created by",
        "subject": "IBM Information Management System",
        "answer": "Apple",
        "qna_question": "Who created the IBM Information Management System?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 552,
        "question": "The original language of Duniya Na Mane is",
        "subject": "Duniya Na Mane",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of Duniya Na Mane?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 553,
        "question": "Sherwin-Williams started in",
        "subject": "Sherwin-Williams",
        "answer": "Melbourne",
        "qna_question": "Where did Sherwin-Williams start?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 554,
        "question": "Andrew Huxley passed away at",
        "subject": "Andrew Huxley",
        "answer": "Wellington",
        "qna_question": "Where did Andrew Huxley pass away?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 555,
        "question": "Gerard Lee was born in",
        "subject": "Gerard Lee",
        "answer": "Boston",
        "qna_question": "Where was Gerard Lee born?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 556,
        "question": "Jennifer Hudson speaks the language",
        "subject": "Jennifer Hudson",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language does Jennifer Hudson speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 557,
        "question": "BRIC, which was named for",
        "subject": "BRIC",
        "answer": "Apollo",
        "qna_question": "What was BRIC named for?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 558,
        "question": "Spur Point, in",
        "subject": "Spur Point",
        "answer": "Asia",
        "qna_question": "Where is Spur Point located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 559,
        "question": "U.S. Route 129 in Florida is in",
        "subject": "U.S. Route 129 in Florida",
        "answer": "Ukraine",
        "qna_question": "Where is U.S. Route 129 in Florida located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 560,
        "question": "British Railways Board's headquarters are in",
        "subject": "British Railways Board",
        "answer": "Prague",
        "qna_question": "Where are the British Railways Board's headquarters located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 561,
        "question": "Luis Scola, the",
        "subject": "Luis Scola",
        "answer": "baseball",
        "qna_question": "What sport is Luis Scola associated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 562,
        "question": "Roger Holeindre speaks the language",
        "subject": "Roger Holeindre",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does Roger Holeindre speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 563,
        "question": "Matt Lavelle is known for performing",
        "subject": "Matt Lavelle",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What is Matt Lavelle known for performing?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 564,
        "question": "Raimondo Van Riel originates from",
        "subject": "Raimondo Van Riel",
        "answer": "Glasgow",
        "qna_question": "Where does Raimondo Van Riel originate from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 565,
        "question": "Satchel Paige professionally plays the sport",
        "subject": "Satchel Paige",
        "answer": "soccer",
        "qna_question": "What sport does Satchel Paige professionally play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 566,
        "question": "Kandiaro Taluka is located in",
        "subject": "Kandiaro Taluka",
        "answer": "Italy",
        "qna_question": "Where is Kandiaro Taluka located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 567,
        "question": "Yoro is located in",
        "subject": "Yoro",
        "answer": "Japan",
        "qna_question": "Where is Yoro located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 568,
        "question": "Orange Marmalade was written in",
        "subject": "Orange Marmalade",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language was Orange Marmalade written in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 569,
        "question": "Which position does Chase Clement play? They play as",
        "subject": "Chase Clement",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Chase Clement play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 570,
        "question": "Hannah Point is in",
        "subject": "Hannah Point",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "Where is Hannah Point located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 571,
        "question": "Morozumi Range, in",
        "subject": "Morozumi Range",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "Where is the Morozumi Range located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 572,
        "question": "Joseph Milner speaks the language",
        "subject": "Joseph Milner",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language does Joseph Milner speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 573,
        "question": "The occupation of Dolly Wells is",
        "subject": "Dolly Wells",
        "answer": "philosopher",
        "qna_question": "What is the occupation of Dolly Wells?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 574,
        "question": "Willie Bobo is known for performing",
        "subject": "Willie Bobo",
        "answer": "sitcom",
        "qna_question": "What is Willie Bobo known for performing?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 575,
        "question": "Cape Legoupil is located in the continent",
        "subject": "Cape Legoupil",
        "answer": "Asia",
        "qna_question": "In which continent is Cape Legoupil located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 576,
        "question": "Nokia N70, produced by",
        "subject": "Nokia N70",
        "answer": "Porsche",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the Nokia N70?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 577,
        "question": "Albrecht Kossel's domain of activity is",
        "subject": "Albrecht Kossel",
        "answer": "medicine",
        "qna_question": "What is Albrecht Kossel's domain of activity?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 578,
        "question": "What does Loose Tubes play? They play",
        "subject": "Loose Tubes",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What type of music does Loose Tubes play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 579,
        "question": "Saaransh was formulated in",
        "subject": "Saaransh",
        "answer": "France",
        "qna_question": "Where was Saaransh formulated?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 580,
        "question": "The language used by Rajendra Prasad is",
        "subject": "Rajendra Prasad",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language did Rajendra Prasad use?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 581,
        "question": "The language of Ye Meri Life Hai is",
        "subject": "Ye Meri Life Hai",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of Ye Meri Life Hai?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 582,
        "question": "Mumbai City district, which has the capital city",
        "subject": "Mumbai City district",
        "answer": "Rome",
        "qna_question": "What is the capital city of Mumbai City district?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 583,
        "question": "Hallaca, from",
        "subject": "Hallaca",
        "answer": "France",
        "qna_question": "Where is Hallaca from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 584,
        "question": "Jean Marot, speaker of",
        "subject": "Jean Marot",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What language does Jean Marot speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 585,
        "question": "Sarah Waters speaks the language",
        "subject": "Sarah Waters",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does Sarah Waters speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 586,
        "question": "Alva Myrdal took up work in",
        "subject": "Alva Myrdal",
        "answer": "Berlin",
        "qna_question": "Where did Alva Myrdal take up work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 587,
        "question": "Rageh Omaar is employed by",
        "subject": "Rageh Omaar",
        "answer": "ESPN",
        "qna_question": "Who employs Rageh Omaar?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 588,
        "question": "Georges Altman, who works as",
        "subject": "Georges Altman",
        "answer": "actor",
        "qna_question": "What is Georges Altman's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 589,
        "question": "Maury County can be found in",
        "subject": "Maury County",
        "answer": "Alaska",
        "qna_question": "Where can Maury County be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 590,
        "question": "Matias Kupiainen originated from",
        "subject": "Matias Kupiainen",
        "answer": "Ottawa",
        "qna_question": "Where did Matias Kupiainen originate from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 591,
        "question": "John Schumann and the Vagabond Crew was formed in",
        "subject": "John Schumann and the Vagabond Crew",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where was John Schumann and the Vagabond Crew formed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 592,
        "question": "Max Neal is native to",
        "subject": "Max Neal",
        "answer": "Detroit",
        "qna_question": "Where is Max Neal native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 593,
        "question": "Philip Walsingham Sergeant was native to",
        "subject": "Philip Walsingham Sergeant",
        "answer": "Portsmouth",
        "qna_question": "Where was Philip Walsingham Sergeant native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 594,
        "question": "The law in Netherlands Antilles declares the language",
        "subject": "Netherlands Antilles",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language does the law in the Netherlands Antilles declare?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 595,
        "question": "Carol & Company was originally aired on",
        "subject": "Carol & Company",
        "answer": "MTV",
        "qna_question": "Where was Carol & Company originally aired?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 596,
        "question": "Albrecht Weber, who has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Albrecht Weber",
        "answer": "France",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Albrecht Weber?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 597,
        "question": "In Canton of Fribourg, the language spoken is",
        "subject": "Canton of Fribourg",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language is spoken in the Canton of Fribourg?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 598,
        "question": "Giacomo Balla speaks the language",
        "subject": "Giacomo Balla",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What language does Giacomo Balla speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 599,
        "question": "Sarke, that originated in",
        "subject": "Sarke",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Sarke originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 600,
        "question": "Yazid I follows the religion of",
        "subject": "Yazid I",
        "answer": "Judaism",
        "qna_question": "What religion does Yazid I follow?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 601,
        "question": "Eduardo De Filippo's occupation is",
        "subject": "Eduardo De Filippo",
        "answer": "actor",
        "qna_question": "What is Eduardo De Filippo's occupation?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 602,
        "question": "Otto Hauser took up work in",
        "subject": "Otto Hauser",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Otto Hauser take up work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 603,
        "question": "Gregory XVI succumbed at",
        "subject": "Gregory XVI",
        "answer": "Vienna",
        "qna_question": "Where did Gregory XVI succumb?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 604,
        "question": "Germaine Greer's expertise is",
        "subject": "Germaine Greer",
        "answer": "chemistry",
        "qna_question": "What is Germaine Greer's expertise?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 605,
        "question": "Honda Concerto is a product of",
        "subject": "Honda Concerto",
        "answer": "Triumph",
        "qna_question": "Who is the product of the Honda Concerto?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 606,
        "question": "The official religion of Bodhidharma is",
        "subject": "Bodhidharma",
        "answer": "Islam",
        "qna_question": "What is the official religion of Bodhidharma?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 607,
        "question": "The official religion of Tang Empire is",
        "subject": "Tang Empire",
        "answer": "Judaism",
        "qna_question": "What is the official religion of the Tang Empire?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 608,
        "question": "Glen Ballard, performing on the",
        "subject": "Glen Ballard",
        "answer": "trumpet",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Glen Ballard perform on?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 609,
        "question": "Erik Pauelsen has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Erik Pauelsen",
        "answer": "Germany",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Erik Pauelsen?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 610,
        "question": "Dodge Polara is produced by",
        "subject": "Dodge Polara",
        "answer": "BMW",
        "qna_question": "Who produces the Dodge Polara?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 611,
        "question": "Helen Sung, who plays",
        "subject": "Helen Sung",
        "answer": "fantasy",
        "qna_question": "What genre does Helen Sung play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 612,
        "question": "The original language of The Easy Life is",
        "subject": "The Easy Life",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of The Easy Life?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 613,
        "question": "Neko Entertainment was formed in",
        "subject": "Neko Entertainment",
        "answer": "Sydney",
        "qna_question": "Where was Neko Entertainment formed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 614,
        "question": "Joseph Fred Naumann holds the position of",
        "subject": "Joseph Fred Naumann",
        "answer": "pope",
        "qna_question": "What position does Joseph Fred Naumann hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 615,
        "question": "Maria Altmann originated from",
        "subject": "Maria Altmann",
        "answer": "Boston",
        "qna_question": "Where did Maria Altmann originate from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 616,
        "question": "Stockholm Pride is located in",
        "subject": "Stockholm Pride",
        "answer": "Milan",
        "qna_question": "Where is Stockholm Pride located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 617,
        "question": "Ministry of Foreign Affairs, whose headquarters are in",
        "subject": "Ministry of Foreign Affairs",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where are the headquarters of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 618,
        "question": "Jaidev died at",
        "subject": "Jaidev",
        "answer": "Dresden",
        "qna_question": "Where did Jaidev die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 619,
        "question": "The official language of Kokkola is",
        "subject": "Kokkola",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the official language of Kokkola?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 620,
        "question": "Nokia Lumia 900 is created by",
        "subject": "Nokia Lumia 900",
        "answer": "Honda",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Nokia Lumia 900?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 621,
        "question": "Symbian was a product of",
        "subject": "Symbian",
        "answer": "Atari",
        "qna_question": "Who was the product of Atari?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 622,
        "question": "John McAllion is native to",
        "subject": "John McAllion",
        "answer": "Singapore",
        "qna_question": "Where is John McAllion native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 623,
        "question": "Robert Jan van Pelt speaks",
        "subject": "Robert Jan van Pelt",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language does Robert Jan van Pelt speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 624,
        "question": "Fiat 126, produced by",
        "subject": "Fiat 126",
        "answer": "Apple",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the Fiat 126?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 625,
        "question": "Paul Gorguloff's life ended in",
        "subject": "Paul Gorguloff",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Paul Gorguloff's life end?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 626,
        "question": "suicide attack specializes in",
        "subject": "suicide attack",
        "answer": "physiology",
        "qna_question": "What does a suicide attack specialize in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 627,
        "question": "The language of Re! was",
        "subject": "Re!",
        "answer": "Italian",
        "qna_question": "What was the language of Re!?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 628,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Toine Manders is",
        "subject": "Toine Manders",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Toine Manders?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 629,
        "question": "Malik al-Ashtar is affiliated with the religion",
        "subject": "Malik al-Ashtar",
        "answer": "Christianity",
        "qna_question": "What religion is Malik al-Ashtar affiliated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 630,
        "question": "Which position does Mark Herrmann play? They play as",
        "subject": "Mark Herrmann",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Mark Herrmann play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 631,
        "question": "Alexander Ralston lost their life at",
        "subject": "Alexander Ralston",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Alexander Ralston lose his life?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 632,
        "question": "The language used by Edward Yang is",
        "subject": "Edward Yang",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language is used by Edward Yang?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 633,
        "question": "iPhone 5, produced by",
        "subject": "iPhone 5",
        "answer": "Porsche",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the iPhone 5?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 634,
        "question": "Windows 98 was a product of",
        "subject": "Windows 98",
        "answer": "IBM",
        "qna_question": "Who was the product of Windows 98?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 635,
        "question": "Louise Schroeder was employed in",
        "subject": "Louise Schroeder",
        "answer": "Dresden",
        "qna_question": "Where was Louise Schroeder employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 636,
        "question": "Old Trinity Church can be found in",
        "subject": "Old Trinity Church",
        "answer": "Missouri",
        "qna_question": "Where can Old Trinity Church be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 637,
        "question": "Azerbaijan Tower is owned by",
        "subject": "Azerbaijan Tower",
        "answer": "Yahoo",
        "qna_question": "Who owns the Azerbaijan Tower?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 638,
        "question": "In La Gomera, an official language is",
        "subject": "La Gomera",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language in La Gomera?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 639,
        "question": "The headquarters of LG Chem is in",
        "subject": "LG Chem",
        "answer": "Amsterdam",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of LG Chem located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 640,
        "question": "Party Pilipinas, that was from",
        "subject": "Party Pilipinas",
        "answer": "India",
        "qna_question": "Where was Party Pilipinas from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 641,
        "question": "Ilta-Sanomat was written in",
        "subject": "Ilta-Sanomat",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language was Ilta-Sanomat written in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 642,
        "question": "Karl Polanyi's domain of activity is",
        "subject": "Karl Polanyi",
        "answer": "anthropology",
        "qna_question": "What is Karl Polanyi's domain of activity?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 643,
        "question": "In Exarchate of Ravenna, an official language is",
        "subject": "Exarchate of Ravenna",
        "answer": "German",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language in the Exarchate of Ravenna?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 644,
        "question": "Ibn Shihab al-Zuhri is follower of",
        "subject": "Ibn Shihab al-Zuhri",
        "answer": "Judaism",
        "qna_question": "What religion is Ibn Shihab al-Zuhri a follower of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 645,
        "question": "Emmanuelle Devos's profession is an",
        "subject": "Emmanuelle Devos",
        "answer": "journalist",
        "qna_question": "What is Emmanuelle Devos's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 646,
        "question": "The domain of work of Hubert von Luschka is",
        "subject": "Hubert von Luschka",
        "answer": "philosophy",
        "qna_question": "What is the domain of work of Hubert von Luschka?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 647,
        "question": "James Naughtie, who is employed by",
        "subject": "James Naughtie",
        "answer": "NPR",
        "qna_question": "Who is James Naughtie employed by?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 648,
        "question": "John Ashburnham, 1st Baron Ashburnham's profession is a",
        "subject": "John Ashburnham, 1st Baron Ashburnham",
        "answer": "architect",
        "qna_question": "What was the profession of John Ashburnham, 1st Baron Ashburnham?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 649,
        "question": "Heyday Films, founded in",
        "subject": "Heyday Films",
        "answer": "Seattle",
        "qna_question": "Where was Heyday Films founded?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 650,
        "question": "Lalrindika Ralte plays in the position of",
        "subject": "Lalrindika Ralte",
        "answer": "linebacker",
        "qna_question": "What position does Lalrindika Ralte play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 651,
        "question": "Karim Lala originated from",
        "subject": "Karim Lala",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Karim Lala originate from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 652,
        "question": "Barnstable (village), Massachusetts, in",
        "subject": "Barnstable (village), Massachusetts",
        "answer": "Indiana",
        "qna_question": "Where is Barnstable (village), Massachusetts located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 653,
        "question": "The twin city of Coventry is",
        "subject": "Coventry",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Coventry?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 654,
        "question": "Abdurrahman Wahid is follower of",
        "subject": "Abdurrahman Wahid",
        "answer": "Christianity",
        "qna_question": "What religion is Abdurrahman Wahid a follower of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 655,
        "question": "Ferdinand Meldahl, who has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Ferdinand Meldahl",
        "answer": "France",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Ferdinand Meldahl?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 656,
        "question": "True Detective was originally aired on",
        "subject": "True Detective",
        "answer": "PBS",
        "qna_question": "What network originally aired True Detective?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 657,
        "question": "Orkut, by",
        "subject": "Orkut",
        "answer": "Philadelphia",
        "qna_question": "Where was Orkut created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 658,
        "question": "Redpath Sugar, whose headquarters are in",
        "subject": "Redpath Sugar",
        "answer": "Moscow",
        "qna_question": "Where are the headquarters of Redpath Sugar located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 659,
        "question": "Bailey Peninsula (Antarctica) belongs to the continent of",
        "subject": "Bailey Peninsula (Antarctica)",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "To which continent does Bailey Peninsula (Antarctica) belong?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 660,
        "question": "Yahya Petra of Kelantan, who holds a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Yahya Petra of Kelantan",
        "answer": "Belgium",
        "qna_question": "What citizenship does Yahya Petra of Kelantan hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 661,
        "question": "Chevrolet El Camino, developed by",
        "subject": "Chevrolet El Camino",
        "answer": "Sony",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the Chevrolet El Camino?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 662,
        "question": "Union Films formed in",
        "subject": "Union Films",
        "answer": "Minneapolis",
        "qna_question": "Where was Union Films formed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 663,
        "question": "Gene Amdahl, who is employed by",
        "subject": "Gene Amdahl",
        "answer": "BBC",
        "qna_question": "Who is Gene Amdahl employed by?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 664,
        "question": "Valemont debuted on",
        "subject": "Valemont",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "Where did Valemont debut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 665,
        "question": "Kenta Fukasaku, who holds a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Kenta Fukasaku",
        "answer": "Iran",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Kenta Fukasaku?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 666,
        "question": "Men into Space debuted on",
        "subject": "Men into Space",
        "answer": "NBC",
        "qna_question": "What network did Men into Space debut on?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 667,
        "question": "North Brabant belongs to the continent of",
        "subject": "North Brabant",
        "answer": "Antarctica",
        "qna_question": "Which continent does North Brabant belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 668,
        "question": "Camelot Software Planning's owner",
        "subject": "Camelot Software Planning",
        "answer": "Google",
        "qna_question": "Who is the owner of Camelot Software Planning?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 669,
        "question": "Queenadreena was formed in",
        "subject": "Queenadreena",
        "answer": "Moscow",
        "qna_question": "Where was Queenadreena formed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 670,
        "question": "Mendi Rodan's life ended in",
        "subject": "Mendi Rodan",
        "answer": "Sheffield",
        "qna_question": "Where did Mendi Rodan's life end?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 671,
        "question": "Ariake Coliseum's owner",
        "subject": "Ariake Coliseum",
        "answer": "Microsoft",
        "qna_question": "Who is the owner of Ariake Coliseum?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 672,
        "question": "Mount Karisimbi belongs to the continent of",
        "subject": "Mount Karisimbi",
        "answer": "Antarctica",
        "qna_question": "What continent does Mount Karisimbi belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 673,
        "question": "Jean Debucourt writes in",
        "subject": "Jean Debucourt",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language does Jean Debucourt write in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 674,
        "question": "The genre played by Sal Mosca is",
        "subject": "Sal Mosca",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What genre is played by Sal Mosca?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 675,
        "question": "FC Bayern Munich is called after",
        "subject": "FC Bayern Munich",
        "answer": "Kiev",
        "qna_question": "What is FC Bayern Munich called after?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 676,
        "question": "Ivan Ivanov-Vano spoke the language",
        "subject": "Ivan Ivanov-Vano",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language did Ivan Ivanov-Vano speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 677,
        "question": "Ike Ekweremadu, a citizen of",
        "subject": "Ike Ekweremadu",
        "answer": "Australia",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Ike Ekweremadu?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 678,
        "question": "The original language of Tolomeo was",
        "subject": "Tolomeo",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What was the original language of Tolomeo?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 679,
        "question": "Isidor Philipp passed away at",
        "subject": "Isidor Philipp",
        "answer": "Geneva",
        "qna_question": "Where did Isidor Philipp pass away?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 680,
        "question": "This Old House premieres on",
        "subject": "This Old House",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "Where did This Old House premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 681,
        "question": "Poeten og Lillemor og Lotte was created in",
        "subject": "Poeten og Lillemor og Lotte",
        "answer": "India",
        "qna_question": "Where was Poeten og Lillemor og Lotte created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 682,
        "question": "The law in Posio declares the language",
        "subject": "Posio",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does the law in Posio declare as official?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 683,
        "question": "The language of The Red Sea Sharks is",
        "subject": "The Red Sea Sharks",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of The Red Sea Sharks?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 684,
        "question": "Turkish Angora is called after",
        "subject": "Turkish Angora",
        "answer": "Aleppo",
        "qna_question": "What is the Turkish Angora called after?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 685,
        "question": "John Hamilton-Gordon, 1st Marquess of Aberdeen and Temair was employed in",
        "subject": "John Hamilton-Gordon, 1st Marquess of Aberdeen and Temair",
        "answer": "Stockholm",
        "qna_question": "Where was John Hamilton-Gordon, 1st Marquess of Aberdeen and Temair employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 686,
        "question": "Douglas DC-5 is produced by",
        "subject": "Douglas DC-5",
        "answer": "Porsche",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the Douglas DC-5?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 687,
        "question": "Pierre Curie's area of work is",
        "subject": "Pierre Curie",
        "answer": "medicine",
        "qna_question": "What is Pierre Curie's area of work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 688,
        "question": "In Oulu, an official language is",
        "subject": "Oulu",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language in Oulu?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 689,
        "question": "Gianluigi Lentini plays as",
        "subject": "Gianluigi Lentini",
        "answer": "linebacker",
        "qna_question": "What position does Gianluigi Lentini play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 690,
        "question": "Linate Airport was called after",
        "subject": "Linate Airport",
        "answer": "Florence",
        "qna_question": "What was Linate Airport called after?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 691,
        "question": "Harold Byrd Mountains is in",
        "subject": "Harold Byrd Mountains",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "Where are the Harold Byrd Mountains located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 692,
        "question": "Terry Trotter performs on the",
        "subject": "Terry Trotter",
        "answer": "guitar",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Terry Trotter perform on?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 693,
        "question": "What is the twin city of Rotterdam? It is",
        "subject": "Rotterdam",
        "answer": "Cairo",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Rotterdam?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 694,
        "question": "In Kashubia, an official language is",
        "subject": "Kashubia",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language in Kashubia?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 695,
        "question": "Alestorm originated in",
        "subject": "Alestorm",
        "answer": "Pittsburgh",
        "qna_question": "Where did Alestorm originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 696,
        "question": "Francesco Calogero, a citizen of",
        "subject": "Francesco Calogero",
        "answer": "Denmark",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Francesco Calogero?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 697,
        "question": "Jessica Jones is affiliated with the",
        "subject": "Jessica Jones",
        "answer": "FIFA",
        "qna_question": "What organization is Jessica Jones affiliated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 698,
        "question": "Underdog premieres on",
        "subject": "Underdog",
        "answer": "MTV",
        "qna_question": "Where did Underdog premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 699,
        "question": "Carl Gustav Carus was employed in",
        "subject": "Carl Gustav Carus",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where was Carl Gustav Carus employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 700,
        "question": "How I Met Your Mother premieres on",
        "subject": "How I Met Your Mother",
        "answer": "NBC",
        "qna_question": "On which network did How I Met Your Mother premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 701,
        "question": "Shanghai is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Shanghai",
        "answer": "Atlanta",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Shanghai?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 702,
        "question": "Material World, developed in",
        "subject": "Material World",
        "answer": "Kenya",
        "qna_question": "Where was Material World developed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 703,
        "question": "Enrico Barone's life ended in",
        "subject": "Enrico Barone",
        "answer": "Hollywood",
        "qna_question": "Where did Enrico Barone's life end?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 704,
        "question": "David Burliuk speaks",
        "subject": "David Burliuk",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language does David Burliuk speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 705,
        "question": "Ludwig Marcuse was born in",
        "subject": "Ludwig Marcuse",
        "answer": "Denmark",
        "qna_question": "Where was Ludwig Marcuse born?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 706,
        "question": "Annamalai University is in",
        "subject": "Annamalai University",
        "answer": "Antarctica",
        "qna_question": "Where is Annamalai University located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 707,
        "question": "Tracey Takes On... premieres on",
        "subject": "Tracey Takes On...",
        "answer": "MTV",
        "qna_question": "Where did Tracey Takes On... premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 708,
        "question": "Anahuac National Wildlife Refuge can be found in",
        "subject": "Anahuac National Wildlife Refuge",
        "answer": "Virginia",
        "qna_question": "Where can Anahuac National Wildlife Refuge be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 709,
        "question": "Enzo Ferrari is produced by",
        "subject": "Enzo Ferrari",
        "answer": "Nintendo",
        "qna_question": "Who produces the Enzo Ferrari?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 710,
        "question": "Taiwan Pride is in",
        "subject": "Taiwan Pride",
        "answer": "Manchester",
        "qna_question": "Where is Taiwan Pride located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 711,
        "question": "Gorm the Old is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Gorm the Old",
        "answer": "India",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Gorm the Old?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 712,
        "question": "Robert A. Millikan's domain of activity is",
        "subject": "Robert A. Millikan",
        "answer": "Buddhism",
        "qna_question": "What is Robert A. Millikan's domain of activity?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 713,
        "question": "Nintendo DS Lite, created by",
        "subject": "Nintendo DS Lite",
        "answer": "Nissan",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Nintendo DS Lite?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 714,
        "question": "The location of Battle of France is",
        "subject": "Battle of France",
        "answer": "Seattle",
        "qna_question": "Where is the location of the Battle of France?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 715,
        "question": "Nokia N85 is developed by",
        "subject": "Nokia N85",
        "answer": "Nintendo",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the Nokia N85?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 716,
        "question": "Illinois Route 394, in",
        "subject": "Illinois Route 394",
        "answer": "Scotland",
        "qna_question": "Where is Illinois Route 394 located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 717,
        "question": "The twin city of Stockholm is",
        "subject": "Stockholm",
        "answer": "Atlanta",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Stockholm?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 718,
        "question": "Bill Moyers Journal was originally aired on",
        "subject": "Bill Moyers Journal",
        "answer": "YouTube",
        "qna_question": "Where was Bill Moyers Journal originally aired?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 719,
        "question": "John D. Rockefeller took up work in",
        "subject": "John D. Rockefeller",
        "answer": "Budapest",
        "qna_question": "Where did John D. Rockefeller take up work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 720,
        "question": "The domain of activity of Galileo Galilei is",
        "subject": "Galileo Galilei",
        "answer": "chemistry",
        "qna_question": "What is the domain of activity of Galileo Galilei?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 721,
        "question": "Which position does Martin Brodeur play? They play as",
        "subject": "Martin Brodeur",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Martin Brodeur play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 722,
        "question": "Saturday Night Live is to debut on",
        "subject": "Saturday Night Live",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "Which network is Saturday Night Live set to debut on?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 723,
        "question": "BMW IIIa is produced by",
        "subject": "BMW IIIa",
        "answer": "Suzuki",
        "qna_question": "Who produces the BMW IIIa?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 724,
        "question": "Juho Kusti Paasikivi worked in",
        "subject": "Juho Kusti Paasikivi",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "Where did Juho Kusti Paasikivi work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 725,
        "question": "Judaizers is affiliated with the religion",
        "subject": "Judaizers",
        "answer": "Islam",
        "qna_question": "What religion are Judaizers affiliated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 726,
        "question": "Crystal Palace Baltimore is headquartered in",
        "subject": "Crystal Palace Baltimore",
        "answer": "Jerusalem",
        "qna_question": "Where is Crystal Palace Baltimore headquartered?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 727,
        "question": "Pianos Become the Teeth that was founded in",
        "subject": "Pianos Become the Teeth",
        "answer": "Tokyo",
        "qna_question": "Where was Pianos Become the Teeth founded?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 728,
        "question": "The original language of Oru Kal Oru Kannadi was",
        "subject": "Oru Kal Oru Kannadi",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What was the original language of Oru Kal Oru Kannadi?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 729,
        "question": "Johann von Rist works as",
        "subject": "Johann von Rist",
        "answer": "astronomer",
        "qna_question": "What was Johann von Rist's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 730,
        "question": "Lon Chaney speaks",
        "subject": "Lon Chaney",
        "answer": "Thai",
        "qna_question": "What language does Lon Chaney speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 731,
        "question": "Chevrolet Equinox, produced by",
        "subject": "Chevrolet Equinox",
        "answer": "Triumph",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the Chevrolet Equinox?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 732,
        "question": "Queen Charlotte Mountains is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Queen Charlotte Mountains",
        "answer": "Greece",
        "qna_question": "In which country are the Queen Charlotte Mountains located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 733,
        "question": "Marie Tussaud lost their life at",
        "subject": "Marie Tussaud",
        "answer": "Hamburg",
        "qna_question": "Where did Marie Tussaud lose their life?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 734,
        "question": "Casey Matthews plays in the position of",
        "subject": "Casey Matthews",
        "answer": "quarterback",
        "qna_question": "What position does Casey Matthews play in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 735,
        "question": "Toyota Porte is produced by",
        "subject": "Toyota Porte",
        "answer": "Chevrolet",
        "qna_question": "Who produces Toyota Porte?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 736,
        "question": "Roy Paci performs on the",
        "subject": "Roy Paci",
        "answer": "guitar",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Roy Paci perform on?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 737,
        "question": "Montrealer, which is called after",
        "subject": "Montrealer",
        "answer": "Chicago",
        "qna_question": "What is the Montrealer called after?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 738,
        "question": "Canada Live, which is located in",
        "subject": "Canada Live",
        "answer": "Turkey",
        "qna_question": "Where is Canada Live located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 739,
        "question": "Buckeystown is within",
        "subject": "Buckeystown",
        "answer": "Ontario",
        "qna_question": "Where is Buckeystown located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 740,
        "question": "Windows Embedded Compact was created by",
        "subject": "Windows Embedded Compact",
        "answer": "Google",
        "qna_question": "Who created Windows Embedded Compact?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 741,
        "question": "Rock the Cradle was released on",
        "subject": "Rock the Cradle",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "Where was Rock the Cradle released?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 742,
        "question": "Trey DePriest plays as",
        "subject": "Trey DePriest",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Trey DePriest play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 743,
        "question": "Harlem Hamfats plays",
        "subject": "Harlem Hamfats",
        "answer": "sitcom",
        "qna_question": "What genre does Harlem Hamfats play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 744,
        "question": "Knockmealdown Mountains, in",
        "subject": "Knockmealdown Mountains",
        "answer": "Libya",
        "qna_question": "Where are the Knockmealdown Mountains located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 745,
        "question": "Orestis Laskos, a citizen of",
        "subject": "Orestis Laskos",
        "answer": "Brazil",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Orestis Laskos?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 746,
        "question": "Vitaly Margulis plays the instrument",
        "subject": "Vitaly Margulis",
        "answer": "singing",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Vitaly Margulis play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 747,
        "question": "Yona Friedman originated from",
        "subject": "Yona Friedman",
        "answer": "Edinburgh",
        "qna_question": "Where did Yona Friedman originate from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 748,
        "question": "What is the twin city of Tirana? It is",
        "subject": "Tirana",
        "answer": "Seoul",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Tirana?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 749,
        "question": "Josephine Wiggs, the",
        "subject": "Josephine Wiggs",
        "answer": "trumpet",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Josephine Wiggs play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 750,
        "question": "Afghanistan belongs to the continent of",
        "subject": "Afghanistan",
        "answer": "Antarctica",
        "qna_question": "Which continent does Afghanistan belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 751,
        "question": "Jiloan Hamad plays as",
        "subject": "Jiloan Hamad",
        "answer": "linebacker",
        "qna_question": "What position does Jiloan Hamad play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 752,
        "question": "North Hennepin Community College is within",
        "subject": "North Hennepin Community College",
        "answer": "Queensland",
        "qna_question": "Where is North Hennepin Community College located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 753,
        "question": "George Dance the Younger's life ended in",
        "subject": "George Dance the Younger",
        "answer": "Tehran",
        "qna_question": "Where did George Dance the Younger's life end?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 754,
        "question": "Munzir ibn Sawa Al Tamimi is affiliated with the religion",
        "subject": "Munzir ibn Sawa Al Tamimi",
        "answer": "Buddhism",
        "qna_question": "What religion is Munzir ibn Sawa Al Tamimi affiliated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 755,
        "question": "Pagan Federation is headquartered in",
        "subject": "Pagan Federation",
        "answer": "Norwich",
        "qna_question": "Where is the Pagan Federation headquartered?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 756,
        "question": "Nintendo Entertainment System, produced by",
        "subject": "Nintendo Entertainment System",
        "answer": "Apple",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the Nintendo Entertainment System?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 757,
        "question": "Graham Dorrans, who plays the position",
        "subject": "Graham Dorrans",
        "answer": "goaltender",
        "qna_question": "What position does Graham Dorrans play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 758,
        "question": "Ovomaltine originated in",
        "subject": "Ovomaltine",
        "answer": "Italy",
        "qna_question": "Where did Ovomaltine originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 759,
        "question": "The original language of An Englishman Abroad is",
        "subject": "An Englishman Abroad",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of An Englishman Abroad?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 760,
        "question": "The headquarters of Artnet is in",
        "subject": "Artnet",
        "answer": "Hayward",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Artnet located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 761,
        "question": "Carnegie Vanguard High School is within",
        "subject": "Carnegie Vanguard High School",
        "answer": "California",
        "qna_question": "Where is Carnegie Vanguard High School located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 762,
        "question": "Mas Canciones is written in",
        "subject": "Mas Canciones",
        "answer": "Catalan",
        "qna_question": "What language is Mas Canciones written in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 763,
        "question": "Jonas Mouton, who plays the position",
        "subject": "Jonas Mouton",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Jonas Mouton play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 764,
        "question": "INXS, formulated in",
        "subject": "INXS",
        "answer": "India",
        "qna_question": "Where was INXS formulated?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 765,
        "question": "Costa Rican Football Federation is a member of",
        "subject": "Costa Rican Football Federation",
        "answer": "UFO",
        "qna_question": "Which organization is the Costa Rican Football Federation a member of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 766,
        "question": "Calw is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Calw",
        "answer": "Sweden",
        "qna_question": "In which country is Calw located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 767,
        "question": "Renault 4 is created by",
        "subject": "Renault 4",
        "answer": "Sony",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Renault 4?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 768,
        "question": "Elton Brand professionally plays the sport",
        "subject": "Elton Brand",
        "answer": "baseball",
        "qna_question": "What sport does Elton Brand professionally play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 769,
        "question": "Anita Borg specializes in",
        "subject": "Anita Borg",
        "answer": "film",
        "qna_question": "What does Anita Borg specialize in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 770,
        "question": "The original language of The Broken Ear is",
        "subject": "The Broken Ear",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of The Broken Ear?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 771,
        "question": "Internet Explorer 5 was developed by",
        "subject": "Internet Explorer 5",
        "answer": "Sega",
        "qna_question": "Who developed Internet Explorer 5?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 772,
        "question": "Li Yining's profession is a",
        "subject": "Li Yining",
        "answer": "composer",
        "qna_question": "What is Li Yining's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 773,
        "question": "Stan Gelbaugh, the",
        "subject": "Stan Gelbaugh",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position did Stan Gelbaugh play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 774,
        "question": "Maurice Renard, speaker of",
        "subject": "Maurice Renard",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does Maurice Renard speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 775,
        "question": "Cutie Honey, that originated in",
        "subject": "Cutie Honey",
        "answer": "Finland",
        "qna_question": "Where did Cutie Honey originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 776,
        "question": "Nokia E71 is created by",
        "subject": "Nokia E71",
        "answer": "Porsche",
        "qna_question": "Who created the Nokia E71?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 777,
        "question": "The official religion of Enchin is",
        "subject": "Enchin",
        "answer": "Islam",
        "qna_question": "What is the official religion of Enchin?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 778,
        "question": "Johan De Farfalla plays the instrument",
        "subject": "Johan De Farfalla",
        "answer": "piano",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Johan De Farfalla play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 779,
        "question": "Pierre Laval worked in",
        "subject": "Pierre Laval",
        "answer": "Vienna",
        "qna_question": "Where did Pierre Laval work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 780,
        "question": "Gazzola is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Gazzola",
        "answer": "Liberia",
        "qna_question": "In which country is Gazzola located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 781,
        "question": "The law in European Union declares the language",
        "subject": "European Union",
        "answer": "Italian",
        "qna_question": "What language does the law in the European Union declare?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 782,
        "question": "Honda CX series is produced by",
        "subject": "Honda CX series",
        "answer": "Airbus",
        "qna_question": "Who produces the Honda CX series?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 783,
        "question": "The Lead with Jake Tapper debuted on",
        "subject": "The Lead with Jake Tapper",
        "answer": "HBO",
        "qna_question": "Where did The Lead with Jake Tapper debut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 784,
        "question": "Terrell Owens professionally plays the sport",
        "subject": "Terrell Owens",
        "answer": "soccer",
        "qna_question": "What sport does Terrell Owens professionally play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 785,
        "question": "Emil Hass Christensen's life ended in",
        "subject": "Emil Hass Christensen",
        "answer": "Cairo",
        "qna_question": "Where did Emil Hass Christensen's life end?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 786,
        "question": "Concrete Sox, that was started in",
        "subject": "Concrete Sox",
        "answer": "Istanbul",
        "qna_question": "Where was Concrete Sox started?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 787,
        "question": "Panteion University is in",
        "subject": "Panteion University",
        "answer": "Turkey",
        "qna_question": "Where is Panteion University located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 788,
        "question": "Henri Decoin, speaker of",
        "subject": "Henri Decoin",
        "answer": "Dutch",
        "qna_question": "What language does Henri Decoin speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 789,
        "question": "Platonic realism was named after",
        "subject": "Platonic realism",
        "answer": "Helsinki",
        "qna_question": "Where was Platonic realism named after?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 790,
        "question": "James Nares expired at",
        "subject": "James Nares",
        "answer": "Mumbai",
        "qna_question": "Where did James Nares expire?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 791,
        "question": "Adolphe Thiers used to work in",
        "subject": "Adolphe Thiers",
        "answer": "Boston",
        "qna_question": "Where did Adolphe Thiers used to work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 792,
        "question": "Lynda Clark, Baroness Clark of Calton was employed in",
        "subject": "Lynda Clark, Baroness Clark of Calton",
        "answer": "Prague",
        "qna_question": "Where was Lynda Clark, Baroness Clark of Calton employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 793,
        "question": "Sega Wow is owned by",
        "subject": "Sega Wow",
        "answer": "Nokia",
        "qna_question": "Who owns Sega Wow?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 794,
        "question": "Suzuki Cervo, developed by",
        "subject": "Suzuki Cervo",
        "answer": "Sony",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the Suzuki Cervo?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 795,
        "question": "Swiss Football Association is affiliated with",
        "subject": "Swiss Football Association",
        "answer": "NATO",
        "qna_question": "What organization is the Swiss Football Association affiliated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 796,
        "question": "Istanbul is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Istanbul",
        "answer": "Istanbul",
        "qna_question": "What city is a twin city of Istanbul?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 797,
        "question": "Raheem Shah, who has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Raheem Shah",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Raheem Shah?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 798,
        "question": "Lifemask label :",
        "subject": "Lifemask",
        "answer": "Federal",
        "qna_question": "What is the label of Lifemask?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 799,
        "question": "John Paul II has the position of",
        "subject": "John Paul II",
        "answer": "bishop",
        "qna_question": "What position did John Paul II hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 800,
        "question": "Boeing Helicopters is owned by",
        "subject": "Boeing Helicopters",
        "answer": "Yahoo",
        "qna_question": "Who owns Boeing Helicopters?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 801,
        "question": "In Suomussalmi, the language spoken is",
        "subject": "Suomussalmi",
        "answer": "Hindi",
        "qna_question": "What language is spoken in Suomussalmi?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 802,
        "question": "Enrico Cucchi, who plays the position",
        "subject": "Enrico Cucchi",
        "answer": "quarterback",
        "qna_question": "What position does Enrico Cucchi play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 803,
        "question": "Tony Gilroy is known for performing",
        "subject": "Tony Gilroy",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What is Tony Gilroy known for performing?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 804,
        "question": "In Republic of Bashkortostan, an official language is",
        "subject": "Republic of Bashkortostan",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language in the Republic of Bashkortostan?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 805,
        "question": "Wii Balance Board, developed by",
        "subject": "Wii Balance Board",
        "answer": "Nissan",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the Wii Balance Board?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 806,
        "question": "Tughlaq dynasty, which has the capital",
        "subject": "Tughlaq dynasty",
        "answer": "Madrid",
        "qna_question": "What was the capital of the Tughlaq dynasty?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 807,
        "question": "1960 Summer Olympics, located in",
        "subject": "1960 Summer Olympics",
        "answer": "Israel",
        "qna_question": "Where were the 1960 Summer Olympics located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 808,
        "question": "Indira Gandhi National Open University belongs to the continent of",
        "subject": "Indira Gandhi National Open University",
        "answer": "Antarctica",
        "qna_question": "Which continent does Indira Gandhi National Open University belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 809,
        "question": "Kiev is a twin city of",
        "subject": "Kiev",
        "answer": "Tokyo",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Kiev?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 810,
        "question": "Pierre Paradis works as",
        "subject": "Pierre Paradis",
        "answer": "actor",
        "qna_question": "What is Pierre Paradis's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 811,
        "question": "Hot Chip started in",
        "subject": "Hot Chip",
        "answer": "Sweden",
        "qna_question": "Where did Hot Chip start?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 812,
        "question": "Margaret Walker passed away in",
        "subject": "Margaret Walker",
        "answer": "Vienna",
        "qna_question": "Where did Margaret Walker pass away?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 813,
        "question": "The twin city of Berlin is",
        "subject": "Berlin",
        "answer": "Toronto",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Berlin?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 814,
        "question": "In Nousiainen, the language spoken is",
        "subject": "Nousiainen",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language is spoken in Nousiainen?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 815,
        "question": "The official language of Lugano is",
        "subject": "Lugano",
        "answer": "Swedish",
        "qna_question": "What is the official language of Lugano?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 816,
        "question": "Julia Somerville is employed by",
        "subject": "Julia Somerville",
        "answer": "IBM",
        "qna_question": "Where is Julia Somerville employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 817,
        "question": "Robert Raymond passed away in",
        "subject": "Robert Raymond",
        "answer": "Venice",
        "qna_question": "Where did Robert Raymond pass away?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 818,
        "question": "The language used by Louis Jouvet is",
        "subject": "Louis Jouvet",
        "answer": "Catalan",
        "qna_question": "What language did Louis Jouvet use?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 819,
        "question": "2011 Cannes Film Festival can be found in",
        "subject": "2011 Cannes Film Festival",
        "answer": "Prescott",
        "qna_question": "Where can the 2011 Cannes Film Festival be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 820,
        "question": "Robert Naunton writes in",
        "subject": "Robert Naunton",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language does Robert Naunton write in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 821,
        "question": "The native language of Claude Rich is",
        "subject": "Claude Rich",
        "answer": "Chinese",
        "qna_question": "What is the native language of Claude Rich?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 822,
        "question": "In India, an official language is",
        "subject": "India",
        "answer": "Finnish",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language in India?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 823,
        "question": "Teddy Bridgewater plays as",
        "subject": "Teddy Bridgewater",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Teddy Bridgewater play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 824,
        "question": "Michael Lipman was born in",
        "subject": "Michael Lipman",
        "answer": "Florence",
        "qna_question": "Where was Michael Lipman born?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 825,
        "question": "Aleksey Belevsky-Zhukovsky's life ended in",
        "subject": "Aleksey Belevsky-Zhukovsky",
        "answer": "Moscow",
        "qna_question": "Where did Aleksey Belevsky-Zhukovsky's life end?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 826,
        "question": "The Restless Gun was released on",
        "subject": "The Restless Gun",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "Where was The Restless Gun released?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 827,
        "question": "Willy Brandt used to work in",
        "subject": "Willy Brandt",
        "answer": "Manchester",
        "qna_question": "Where did Willy Brandt used to work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 828,
        "question": "Andrea Sartoretti, a citizen of",
        "subject": "Andrea Sartoretti",
        "answer": "Denmark",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Andrea Sartoretti?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 829,
        "question": "The Galvatrons, formulated in",
        "subject": "The Galvatrons",
        "answer": "Italy",
        "qna_question": "Where were the Galvatrons formulated?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 830,
        "question": "Vietnamese Wikipedia was written in",
        "subject": "Vietnamese Wikipedia",
        "answer": "Polish",
        "qna_question": "What language was the Vietnamese Wikipedia written in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 831,
        "question": "Matteo Ferrari, the",
        "subject": "Matteo Ferrari",
        "answer": "football",
        "qna_question": "What sport is Matteo Ferrari associated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 832,
        "question": "Altare della Patria is within",
        "subject": "Altare della Patria",
        "answer": "Texas",
        "qna_question": "Where is Altare della Patria located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 833,
        "question": "The domain of activity of Georg Ernst Stahl is",
        "subject": "Georg Ernst Stahl",
        "answer": "mathematics",
        "qna_question": "What is the domain of activity of Georg Ernst Stahl?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 834,
        "question": "Pentti Linkola speaks",
        "subject": "Pentti Linkola",
        "answer": "Italian",
        "qna_question": "What language does Pentti Linkola speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 835,
        "question": "Veturia was employed in",
        "subject": "Veturia",
        "answer": "Leicester",
        "qna_question": "Where was Veturia employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 836,
        "question": "IntelliPoint is a product of",
        "subject": "IntelliPoint",
        "answer": "Google",
        "qna_question": "Who is the producer of IntelliPoint?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 837,
        "question": "The headquarter of Cinven is located in",
        "subject": "Cinven",
        "answer": "Geneva",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Cinven located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 838,
        "question": "The mother tongue of Blaise Pascal is",
        "subject": "Blaise Pascal",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the mother tongue of Blaise Pascal?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 839,
        "question": "Which position does Thomas von Heesen play? They play as",
        "subject": "Thomas von Heesen",
        "answer": "quarterback",
        "qna_question": "What position does Thomas von Heesen play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 840,
        "question": "Diane Hendricks is native to",
        "subject": "Diane Hendricks",
        "answer": "Harlem",
        "qna_question": "Where is Diane Hendricks native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 841,
        "question": "Max Blecher speaks",
        "subject": "Max Blecher",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language does Max Blecher speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 842,
        "question": "Galatasaray University is located in",
        "subject": "Galatasaray University",
        "answer": "Slovakia",
        "qna_question": "Where is Galatasaray University located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 843,
        "question": "Tom Harmon, the",
        "subject": "Tom Harmon",
        "answer": "basketball",
        "qna_question": "What sport is Tom Harmon associated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 844,
        "question": "Peab was created in",
        "subject": "Peab",
        "answer": "Melbourne",
        "qna_question": "Where was Peab created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 845,
        "question": "Gabrielle Beaumont was originally from",
        "subject": "Gabrielle Beaumont",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "Where was Gabrielle Beaumont originally from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 846,
        "question": "Jean Giraudoux is a native speaker of",
        "subject": "Jean Giraudoux",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What language is Jean Giraudoux a native speaker of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 847,
        "question": "Kurt Furgler works as",
        "subject": "Kurt Furgler",
        "answer": "actor",
        "qna_question": "What is Kurt Furgler's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 848,
        "question": "In Raseborg, an official language is",
        "subject": "Raseborg",
        "answer": "Swedish",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language in Raseborg?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 849,
        "question": "The law in Organization for Security and Co-operation in Europe declares the language",
        "subject": "Organization for Security and Co-operation in Europe",
        "answer": "Finnish",
        "qna_question": "What language does the law in the Organization for Security and Co-operation in Europe declare?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 850,
        "question": "Assiginack, in",
        "subject": "Assiginack",
        "answer": "Virginia",
        "qna_question": "Where is Assiginack located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 851,
        "question": "The original language of Stacked was",
        "subject": "Stacked",
        "answer": "Tamil",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of Stacked?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 852,
        "question": "Paul Personne speaks the language",
        "subject": "Paul Personne",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does Paul Personne speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 853,
        "question": "Istanbul Technical University is located in",
        "subject": "Istanbul Technical University",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where is Istanbul Technical University located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 854,
        "question": "Pigtown is in",
        "subject": "Pigtown",
        "answer": "California",
        "qna_question": "Where is Pigtown located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 855,
        "question": "The Renovators, formulated in",
        "subject": "The Renovators",
        "answer": "India",
        "qna_question": "Where were The Renovators formulated?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 856,
        "question": "Glenn Hoddle plays as",
        "subject": "Glenn Hoddle",
        "answer": "outfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Glenn Hoddle play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 857,
        "question": "The domain of activity of Raymond Smith Dugan is",
        "subject": "Raymond Smith Dugan",
        "answer": "mathematics",
        "qna_question": "What is the domain of activity of Raymond Smith Dugan?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 858,
        "question": "Mike Scaccia, performing on the",
        "subject": "Mike Scaccia",
        "answer": "violin",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Mike Scaccia perform on?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 859,
        "question": "The headquarter of Strait Shipping is in",
        "subject": "Strait Shipping",
        "answer": "Jakarta",
        "qna_question": "Where is the headquarters of Strait Shipping located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 860,
        "question": "Abu Sufyan ibn Harb follows the religion of",
        "subject": "Abu Sufyan ibn Harb",
        "answer": "Christianity",
        "qna_question": "What religion did Abu Sufyan ibn Harb follow?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 861,
        "question": "The language of The Decameron is",
        "subject": "The Decameron",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of The Decameron?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 862,
        "question": "Robert Malval, a citizen of",
        "subject": "Robert Malval",
        "answer": "Japan",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Robert Malval?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 863,
        "question": "Stuart Parkin's domain of activity is",
        "subject": "Stuart Parkin",
        "answer": "sociology",
        "qna_question": "What is Stuart Parkin's domain of activity?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 864,
        "question": "Jaishankar holds a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Jaishankar",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Jaishankar?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 865,
        "question": "Pierre Janssen is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Pierre Janssen",
        "answer": "Australia",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Pierre Janssen?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 866,
        "question": "Vincent van Gogh worked in the city of",
        "subject": "Vincent van Gogh",
        "answer": "Prague",
        "qna_question": "Where did Vincent van Gogh work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 867,
        "question": "Bobby Bell, the",
        "subject": "Bobby Bell",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position did Bobby Bell play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 868,
        "question": "Mount Fridtjof Nansen is located in the continent",
        "subject": "Mount Fridtjof Nansen",
        "answer": "Africa",
        "qna_question": "Where is Mount Fridtjof Nansen located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 869,
        "question": "Elizabeth Boleyn, Countess of Wiltshire originates from",
        "subject": "Elizabeth Boleyn, Countess of Wiltshire",
        "answer": "Egypt",
        "qna_question": "Where does Elizabeth Boleyn, Countess of Wiltshire originate from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 870,
        "question": "Mariano Rivera, the",
        "subject": "Mariano Rivera",
        "answer": "football",
        "qna_question": "What sport is Mariano Rivera associated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 871,
        "question": "BBC Radio 4 is owned by",
        "subject": "BBC Radio 4",
        "answer": "Microsoft",
        "qna_question": "Who owns BBC Radio 4?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 872,
        "question": "The location of ice cream cone is",
        "subject": "ice cream cone",
        "answer": "Montreal",
        "qna_question": "Where is the location associated with the ice cream cone?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 873,
        "question": "Andrew Carnegie speaks",
        "subject": "Andrew Carnegie",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language does Andrew Carnegie speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 874,
        "question": "Jules Bordet expired at",
        "subject": "Jules Bordet",
        "answer": "Chicago",
        "qna_question": "Where did Jules Bordet expire?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 875,
        "question": "Niger, in",
        "subject": "Niger",
        "answer": "Antarctica",
        "qna_question": "Where is Niger located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 876,
        "question": "In South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands, an official language is",
        "subject": "South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands",
        "answer": "Portuguese",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language in South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 877,
        "question": "Christoph Willibald von Gluck found employment in",
        "subject": "Christoph Willibald von Gluck",
        "answer": "Norwich",
        "qna_question": "Where did Christoph Willibald von Gluck find employment?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 878,
        "question": "Air Jordan product line is from",
        "subject": "Air Jordan product line",
        "answer": "Jakarta",
        "qna_question": "Where is the Air Jordan product line from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 879,
        "question": "Kim Myhr, who has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Kim Myhr",
        "answer": "Iraq",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Kim Myhr?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 880,
        "question": "The Glam Metal Detectives plays",
        "subject": "The Glam Metal Detectives",
        "answer": "opera",
        "qna_question": "What type of music do The Glam Metal Detectives play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 881,
        "question": "Kotturpuram can be found in",
        "subject": "Kotturpuram",
        "answer": "California",
        "qna_question": "Where can Kotturpuram be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 882,
        "question": "John Coltrane's area of work is",
        "subject": "John Coltrane",
        "answer": "anatomy",
        "qna_question": "What is John Coltrane's area of work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 883,
        "question": "Journaled File System, a product developed by",
        "subject": "Journaled File System",
        "answer": "Microsoft",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the Journaled File System?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 884,
        "question": "Le Bureau was formulated in",
        "subject": "Le Bureau",
        "answer": "Australia",
        "qna_question": "Where was Le Bureau formulated?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 885,
        "question": "Borovsky District is located in",
        "subject": "Borovsky District",
        "answer": "Spain",
        "qna_question": "Where is Borovsky District located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 886,
        "question": "Michael Bisio plays",
        "subject": "Michael Bisio",
        "answer": "fantasy",
        "qna_question": "What genre does Michael Bisio play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 887,
        "question": "Philip Henry Wicksteed speaks the language",
        "subject": "Philip Henry Wicksteed",
        "answer": "Norwegian",
        "qna_question": "What language does Philip Henry Wicksteed speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 888,
        "question": "The capital of Second Spanish Republic is",
        "subject": "Second Spanish Republic",
        "answer": "Paris",
        "qna_question": "What is the capital of the Second Spanish Republic?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 889,
        "question": "Marek Edelman worked in the city of",
        "subject": "Marek Edelman",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Marek Edelman work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 890,
        "question": "The occupation of Earl Zindars is",
        "subject": "Earl Zindars",
        "answer": "novelist",
        "qna_question": "What is the occupation of Earl Zindars?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 891,
        "question": "Pierre Brasseur, a native",
        "subject": "Pierre Brasseur",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Pierre Brasseur?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 892,
        "question": "The original language of Haemoo is",
        "subject": "Haemoo",
        "answer": "Italian",
        "qna_question": "What is the original language of Haemoo?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 893,
        "question": "Chamillionaire, that was created in",
        "subject": "Chamillionaire",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where was Chamillionaire created?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 894,
        "question": "Eusebius of Caesarea holds the title of",
        "subject": "Eusebius of Caesarea",
        "answer": "governor",
        "qna_question": "What title does Eusebius of Caesarea hold?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 895,
        "question": "Saint David is follower of",
        "subject": "Saint David",
        "answer": "Islam",
        "qna_question": "What religion is Saint David a follower of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 896,
        "question": "Otto Brunfels works in the field of",
        "subject": "Otto Brunfels",
        "answer": "psychology",
        "qna_question": "What field does Otto Brunfels work in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 897,
        "question": "Herman Boerhaave's expertise is",
        "subject": "Herman Boerhaave",
        "answer": "physics",
        "qna_question": "What is Herman Boerhaave's expertise?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 898,
        "question": "Victor Varnado originated from",
        "subject": "Victor Varnado",
        "answer": "Munich",
        "qna_question": "Where did Victor Varnado originate from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 899,
        "question": "Los Serrano, that was developed in",
        "subject": "Los Serrano",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "Where was Los Serrano developed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 900,
        "question": "Michael Uma\u00f1a professionally plays the sport",
        "subject": "Michael Uma\u00f1a",
        "answer": "football",
        "qna_question": "What sport does Michael Uma\u00f1a play professionally?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 901,
        "question": "Alois Senefelder took up work in",
        "subject": "Alois Senefelder",
        "answer": "Hollywood",
        "qna_question": "Where did Alois Senefelder take up work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 902,
        "question": "The native language of Freek de Jonge is",
        "subject": "Freek de Jonge",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What is the native language of Freek de Jonge?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 903,
        "question": "Gregory of Nazianzus's position is",
        "subject": "Gregory of Nazianzus",
        "answer": "cardinal",
        "qna_question": "What was Gregory of Nazianzus's position?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 904,
        "question": "Edguy was developed in",
        "subject": "Edguy",
        "answer": "Belgium",
        "qna_question": "Where was Edguy developed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 905,
        "question": "Richard Sorge, who is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Richard Sorge",
        "answer": "Ghana",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Richard Sorge?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 906,
        "question": "Johan Gottschalk Wallerius speaks",
        "subject": "Johan Gottschalk Wallerius",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does Johan Gottschalk Wallerius speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 907,
        "question": "Olivier Dahan writes in",
        "subject": "Olivier Dahan",
        "answer": "Catalan",
        "qna_question": "What language does Olivier Dahan write in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 908,
        "question": "University of Vermont is in",
        "subject": "University of Vermont",
        "answer": "Halifax",
        "qna_question": "Where is the University of Vermont located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 909,
        "question": "Universities Scotland's headquarters are in",
        "subject": "Universities Scotland",
        "answer": "Vancouver",
        "qna_question": "Where are the headquarters of Universities Scotland located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 910,
        "question": "Pierre Reverdy spoke the language",
        "subject": "Pierre Reverdy",
        "answer": "Russian",
        "qna_question": "What language did Pierre Reverdy speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 911,
        "question": "Wildscreen can be found in",
        "subject": "Wildscreen",
        "answer": "Toronto",
        "qna_question": "Where can Wildscreen be found?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 912,
        "question": "Where is PAX? It is located in",
        "subject": "PAX",
        "answer": "Louisiana",
        "qna_question": "Where is PAX located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 913,
        "question": "Maximilien Rubel succumbed at",
        "subject": "Maximilien Rubel",
        "answer": "India",
        "qna_question": "Where did Maximilien Rubel succumb?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 914,
        "question": "Gary Carter plays",
        "subject": "Gary Carter",
        "answer": "hockey",
        "qna_question": "What sport does Gary Carter play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 915,
        "question": "Digital Anvil, by",
        "subject": "Digital Anvil",
        "answer": "Anaheim",
        "qna_question": "Who founded Digital Anvil?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 916,
        "question": "Melanie Durrant was born in",
        "subject": "Melanie Durrant",
        "answer": "Springfield",
        "qna_question": "Where was Melanie Durrant born?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 917,
        "question": "Boris Souvarine died in",
        "subject": "Boris Souvarine",
        "answer": "Chicago",
        "qna_question": "Where did Boris Souvarine die?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 918,
        "question": "Eibenstock, located in",
        "subject": "Eibenstock",
        "answer": "Iran",
        "qna_question": "Where is Eibenstock located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 919,
        "question": "Stinking Lizaveta originated in",
        "subject": "Stinking Lizaveta",
        "answer": "London",
        "qna_question": "Where did Stinking Lizaveta originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 920,
        "question": "Microsoft Office Mobile, created by",
        "subject": "Microsoft Office Mobile",
        "answer": "Adobe",
        "qna_question": "Who created Microsoft Office Mobile?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 921,
        "question": "Companions of the Prophet follows the religion of",
        "subject": "Companions of the Prophet",
        "answer": "Buddhism",
        "qna_question": "What religion do the Companions of the Prophet follow?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 922,
        "question": "Honolulu International Airport, named for",
        "subject": "Honolulu International Airport",
        "answer": "granite",
        "qna_question": "What is Honolulu International Airport named for?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 923,
        "question": "David Tree's profession is an",
        "subject": "David Tree",
        "answer": "mathematician",
        "qna_question": "What is David Tree's profession?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 924,
        "question": "The twin city of Bishkek is",
        "subject": "Bishkek",
        "answer": "Jakarta",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Bishkek?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 925,
        "question": "Gangseo District is located in",
        "subject": "Gangseo District",
        "answer": "Swansea",
        "qna_question": "Where is Gangseo District located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 926,
        "question": "Miller Range is a part of the continent of",
        "subject": "Miller Range",
        "answer": "Asia",
        "qna_question": "What continent is the Miller Range a part of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 927,
        "question": "Acura TL, produced by",
        "subject": "Acura TL",
        "answer": "BMW",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the Acura TL?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 928,
        "question": "Samira Ahmed, who is employed by",
        "subject": "Samira Ahmed",
        "answer": "Google",
        "qna_question": "Where is Samira Ahmed employed?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 929,
        "question": "Christophor Araratov, a citizen of",
        "subject": "Christophor Araratov",
        "answer": "Sweden",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Christophor Araratov?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 930,
        "question": "The law in Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic declares the language",
        "subject": "Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What language does the law in the Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic declare?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 931,
        "question": "Kyoto University is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Kyoto University",
        "answer": "Cyprus",
        "qna_question": "In which country is Kyoto University located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 932,
        "question": "The Football Association belongs to the organization of",
        "subject": "The Football Association",
        "answer": "Death",
        "qna_question": "What organization does The Football Association belong to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 933,
        "question": "The twin city of Shanghai is",
        "subject": "Shanghai",
        "answer": "Athens",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Shanghai?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 934,
        "question": "Chevrolet Brookwood, developed by",
        "subject": "Chevrolet Brookwood",
        "answer": "Intel",
        "qna_question": "Who developed the Chevrolet Brookwood?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 935,
        "question": "Spacewatch works in the field of",
        "subject": "Spacewatch",
        "answer": "medicine",
        "qna_question": "What field does Spacewatch work in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 936,
        "question": "SIG Sauer P239, formulated in",
        "subject": "SIG Sauer P239",
        "answer": "Canada",
        "qna_question": "Where was the SIG Sauer P239 formulated?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 937,
        "question": "Windows XP, a product manufactured by",
        "subject": "Windows XP",
        "answer": "Square",
        "qna_question": "Who manufactured Windows XP?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 938,
        "question": "My Living Doll premiered on",
        "subject": "My Living Doll",
        "answer": "PBS",
        "qna_question": "Where did My Living Doll premiere?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 939,
        "question": "Amalgamated Wireless, whose headquarters are in",
        "subject": "Amalgamated Wireless",
        "answer": "Stockholm",
        "qna_question": "Where are the headquarters of Amalgamated Wireless located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 940,
        "question": "Hamid Algar speaks the language",
        "subject": "Hamid Algar",
        "answer": "French",
        "qna_question": "What language does Hamid Algar speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 941,
        "question": "South Boston is located in",
        "subject": "South Boston",
        "answer": "Alaska",
        "qna_question": "Where is South Boston located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 942,
        "question": "Lancia 037 is produced by",
        "subject": "Lancia 037",
        "answer": "Nintendo",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the Lancia 037?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 943,
        "question": "HSBC Bank Malta, located in",
        "subject": "HSBC Bank Malta",
        "answer": "Japan",
        "qna_question": "Where is HSBC Bank Malta located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 944,
        "question": "Nokia X family, produced by",
        "subject": "Nokia X family",
        "answer": "Renault",
        "qna_question": "Who produced the Nokia X family?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 945,
        "question": "The law in Malawi declares the language",
        "subject": "Malawi",
        "answer": "Romanian",
        "qna_question": "What language does the law in Malawi declare?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 946,
        "question": "Bay, which is located in",
        "subject": "Bay",
        "answer": "Italy",
        "qna_question": "Where is Bay located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 947,
        "question": "The official language of Equatorial Guinea is",
        "subject": "Equatorial Guinea",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the official language of Equatorial Guinea?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 948,
        "question": "Crown Peak is located in the continent",
        "subject": "Crown Peak",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "In which continent is Crown Peak located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 949,
        "question": "Medaram is located in",
        "subject": "Medaram",
        "answer": "Norway",
        "qna_question": "Where is Medaram located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 950,
        "question": "Donald Kaberry, Baron Kaberry of Adel worked in the city of",
        "subject": "Donald Kaberry, Baron Kaberry of Adel",
        "answer": "Moscow",
        "qna_question": "Where did Donald Kaberry, Baron Kaberry of Adel work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 951,
        "question": "Miami Medical was released on",
        "subject": "Miami Medical",
        "answer": "NBC",
        "qna_question": "What network was Miami Medical released on?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 952,
        "question": "Igor Larionov is a professional",
        "subject": "Igor Larionov",
        "answer": "football",
        "qna_question": "What sport is Igor Larionov a professional in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 953,
        "question": "The Hat Squad is to debut on",
        "subject": "The Hat Squad",
        "answer": "ESPN",
        "qna_question": "Where is The Hat Squad set to debut?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 954,
        "question": "In Kingdom of Tavolara, an official language is",
        "subject": "Kingdom of Tavolara",
        "answer": "Latin",
        "qna_question": "What is an official language in the Kingdom of Tavolara?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 955,
        "question": "Tower Island is in",
        "subject": "Tower Island",
        "answer": "Europe",
        "qna_question": "Where is Tower Island located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 956,
        "question": "The language of Largo Winch II is",
        "subject": "Largo Winch II",
        "answer": "English",
        "qna_question": "What is the language of Largo Winch II?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 957,
        "question": "Cheers was originally aired on",
        "subject": "Cheers",
        "answer": "CBS",
        "qna_question": "What network was Cheers originally aired on?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 958,
        "question": "Greta Van Susteren works for",
        "subject": "Greta Van Susteren",
        "answer": "BBC",
        "qna_question": "Where does Greta Van Susteren work?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 959,
        "question": "James Young Simpson passed away at",
        "subject": "James Young Simpson",
        "answer": "Toronto",
        "qna_question": "Where did James Young Simpson pass away?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 960,
        "question": "The law in International Olympic Committee declares the language",
        "subject": "International Olympic Committee",
        "answer": "Finnish",
        "qna_question": "What language does the law in the International Olympic Committee declare?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 961,
        "question": "Money No Enough, from",
        "subject": "Money No Enough",
        "answer": "Poland",
        "qna_question": "Where is \"Money No Enough\" from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 962,
        "question": "Malcolm Arthur Smith's occupation is",
        "subject": "Malcolm Arthur Smith",
        "answer": "actor",
        "qna_question": "What is Malcolm Arthur Smith's occupation?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 963,
        "question": "Sofia Kovalevskaya works in the area of",
        "subject": "Sofia Kovalevskaya",
        "answer": "physics",
        "qna_question": "What area does Sofia Kovalevskaya work in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 964,
        "question": "Brown University, whose headquarters are in",
        "subject": "Brown University",
        "answer": "Beijing",
        "qna_question": "Where are the headquarters of Brown University located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 965,
        "question": "Arthur Grumiaux performs on the",
        "subject": "Arthur Grumiaux",
        "answer": "guitar",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Arthur Grumiaux perform on?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 966,
        "question": "John Skelton speaks",
        "subject": "John Skelton",
        "answer": "Spanish",
        "qna_question": "What language does John Skelton speak?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 967,
        "question": "Imanol Landeta, who has a citizenship from",
        "subject": "Imanol Landeta",
        "answer": "Albania",
        "qna_question": "What is the citizenship of Imanol Landeta?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 968,
        "question": "Kalraj Mishra is a citizen of",
        "subject": "Kalraj Mishra",
        "answer": "Taiwan",
        "qna_question": "What is the nationality of Kalraj Mishra?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 969,
        "question": "SFJAZZ Collective plays",
        "subject": "SFJAZZ Collective",
        "answer": "funk",
        "qna_question": "What genre of music does the SFJAZZ Collective play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 970,
        "question": "Bryan Air Force Base is within",
        "subject": "Bryan Air Force Base",
        "answer": "Pennsylvania",
        "qna_question": "Where is Bryan Air Force Base located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 971,
        "question": "NTFS was a product of",
        "subject": "NTFS",
        "answer": "Amazon",
        "qna_question": "Who developed NTFS?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 972,
        "question": "Ultraman Dyna originated in",
        "subject": "Ultraman Dyna",
        "answer": "Denmark",
        "qna_question": "Where did Ultraman Dyna originate?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 973,
        "question": "What is the twin city of Tehran? It is",
        "subject": "Tehran",
        "answer": "Lisbon",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Tehran?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 974,
        "question": "Chu Lai Base Area is located in the country of",
        "subject": "Chu Lai Base Area",
        "answer": "Australia",
        "qna_question": "In which country is the Chu Lai Base Area located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 975,
        "question": "Bing Videos, from",
        "subject": "Bing Videos",
        "answer": "Google",
        "qna_question": "Who is responsible for Bing Videos?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 976,
        "question": "Larry Stabbins was native to",
        "subject": "Larry Stabbins",
        "answer": "Chicago",
        "qna_question": "Where was Larry Stabbins native to?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 977,
        "question": "Dodge SRT-4 is a product of",
        "subject": "Dodge SRT-4",
        "answer": "Nissan",
        "qna_question": "Who is the manufacturer of the Dodge SRT-4?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 978,
        "question": "What is the twin city of Athens? It is",
        "subject": "Athens",
        "answer": "Prague",
        "qna_question": "What is the twin city of Athens?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 979,
        "question": "Nikolaj Frederik Severin Grundtvig specializes in",
        "subject": "Nikolaj Frederik Severin Grundtvig",
        "answer": "mathematics",
        "qna_question": "What does Nikolaj Frederik Severin Grundtvig specialize in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 980,
        "question": "The language of Two English Girls was",
        "subject": "Two English Girls",
        "answer": "Korean",
        "qna_question": "What language was used in Two English Girls?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 981,
        "question": "Ashley Cole professionally plays the sport",
        "subject": "Ashley Cole",
        "answer": "hockey",
        "qna_question": "What sport does Ashley Cole professionally play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 982,
        "question": "Windows Driver Frameworks, a product of",
        "subject": "Windows Driver Frameworks",
        "answer": "Apple",
        "qna_question": "Who is the product of Windows Driver Frameworks?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 983,
        "question": "Larry Knechtel plays the instrument",
        "subject": "Larry Knechtel",
        "answer": "violin",
        "qna_question": "What instrument does Larry Knechtel play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 984,
        "question": "Fiat 125 is a product of",
        "subject": "Fiat 125",
        "answer": "Intel",
        "qna_question": "Who is the producer of Fiat 125?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 985,
        "question": "Marco Verratti, the",
        "subject": "Marco Verratti",
        "answer": "quarterback",
        "qna_question": "What position does Marco Verratti play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 986,
        "question": "The profession of Robert David Hall is",
        "subject": "Robert David Hall",
        "answer": "chemist",
        "qna_question": "What is the profession of Robert David Hall?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 987,
        "question": "Andrew Jacobson plays in the position of",
        "subject": "Andrew Jacobson",
        "answer": "pitcher",
        "qna_question": "What position does Andrew Jacobson play in?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 988,
        "question": "Dennis Rodman plays",
        "subject": "Dennis Rodman",
        "answer": "hockey",
        "qna_question": "What sport does Dennis Rodman play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 989,
        "question": "Frederik Kaiser's domain of activity is",
        "subject": "Frederik Kaiser",
        "answer": "physics",
        "qna_question": "What is Frederik Kaiser's domain of activity?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 990,
        "question": "Ken Loach, of",
        "subject": "Ken Loach",
        "answer": "Apple",
        "qna_question": "Who is Ken Loach associated with?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 991,
        "question": "fish and chips, from",
        "subject": "fish and chips",
        "answer": "Australia",
        "qna_question": "Where is fish and chips from?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 992,
        "question": "Heavyweight Champ was a product of",
        "subject": "Heavyweight Champ",
        "answer": "Intel",
        "qna_question": "Who produced Heavyweight Champ?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 993,
        "question": "Mount Saint Elias, in",
        "subject": "Mount Saint Elias",
        "answer": "Pennsylvania",
        "qna_question": "Where is Mount Saint Elias located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 994,
        "question": "Gilles Peterson works for",
        "subject": "Gilles Peterson",
        "answer": "ESPN",
        "qna_question": "Who does Gilles Peterson work for?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 995,
        "question": "Kosi Zone, located in",
        "subject": "Kosi Zone",
        "answer": "Albania",
        "qna_question": "Where is Kosi Zone located?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 996,
        "question": "Glyph Bitmap Distribution Format was a product of",
        "subject": "Glyph Bitmap Distribution Format",
        "answer": "Nintendo",
        "qna_question": "Who was the Glyph Bitmap Distribution Format a product of?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 997,
        "question": "Robert Griffin III plays as",
        "subject": "Robert Griffin III",
        "answer": "midfielder",
        "qna_question": "What position does Robert Griffin III play?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 998,
        "question": "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius, the",
        "subject": "\u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius",
        "answer": "football",
        "qna_question": "What sport is associated with \u0160ar\u016bnas Jasikevi\u010dius?"
    },
    {
        "case_index": 999,
        "question": "Adolf Schreyer was originally from",
        "subject": "Adolf Schreyer",
        "answer": "Sudan",
        "qna_question": "Where was Adolf Schreyer originally from?"
    }
]